<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: automation | Sweet Distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/automation/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-28T09:50:41+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workflow 1.1: Deeper iOS Automation]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/workflow-iOS-automation/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-03T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/workflow-iOS-automation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="www.macstories.net">MacStories</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>In a few months (I first started testing Workflow in August 2014), Workflow has become an essential component of how I get work done on iOS. The improvements and features launched today extend the app’s capabilities deeper into native iOS frameworks – whether you want to find photos, filter files and calendar events, or save selections from Safari, Workflow is becoming a command center for iOS that can do anything. It’s powerful, and there are still a few issues to fix, but it’s useful, and, even better, it’s fun.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>I’ve tweeted about Workflow several time and if you need a good place to start then look no further. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hammerspoon]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-17T17:42:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you’re into workflow automation, then you might want to check this out. Hammerspoon is Lua based scripting engine for OS X. Just write the code in Lua language and it can interact with OS X APIs such as: clipboard, mouse pointers,filesystem objects, audio, batteries, and more.</p>

<p>If your nerdy side is kickin’ out then why not to try this?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Better Way To Combine iPhone Screenshots with Keyboard Maestro]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/combine-apple-screenshot-using-keyboard-maestro/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-03T17:09:30+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/combine-apple-screenshot-using-keyboard-maestro</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> via <a href="http://www.macstories.net/">Macstories</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>This is one of my most-used Keyboard Maestro macros on a daily basis: it allows me to produce good-looking iPhone screenshots that fit better together with a single keystroke. It literally takes 2 seconds to complete, instead of the couple of minutes you would spend in Acorn or Photoshop to resize, paste, and align.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Menulis artikel tips dan trik untuk sebuah blog teknologi lokal terkadang dituntut adanya screenshot untuk mempermudah pemahaman dari topik yang sedang dibahas. Sebelumnya, untuk menggabungkan beberapa screenshot saya akan membuka Pixelmator dan menyusunnya. Hal ini tentu kurang efektif dan memakan waktu.</p>

<p>Hari ini saya gembira karena menemukan artikel mengenai penggunaan Keyboard Maestro untuk melakukan resize screenshot dari iPhone dan menggabungkannya. Jika biasanya saya menggunakan Pixelmator untuk mengedit dan menggabungkan screenshot memakan waktu lebih dari 15 menit maka dengan macro dari <a href="http://twitter.com/macdrifter">Gabe</a> yang dibahas oleh <a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> tersebut kini hanya perlu waktu kurang dari 5 detik.</p>

<p>Artikel diatas memang sudah cukup lumayan lama mengingat jika dilihat dari published date sudah lebih dari dua tahun berlalu, dan mungkin waktu itu saya masih asik hanya menonton film menggunakan Macbook White yang kini sudah pensiun. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with JavaScript for Automation on Yosemite]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/javascript-for-automation/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-03T10:31:41+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/javascript-for-automation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/The_Axx">Alex Guyot</a> via <a href="www.macstories.net">Macstories</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Automating applications on OS X is an extremely powerful ability, and can save you huge amounts of time. My simple iTunes automation scripts are just conveniences, but the ideas behind them can be appropriated to other, more powerful apps to great effect. If you take the time to evaluate some of your common Mac workflows and take a look at the built-in methods in the productivity apps you use most, you may find that you can use JXA to greatly enhance your efficiency at certain tasks.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Jika <a href="https://developer.apple.com/library/mac/documentation/AppleScript/Conceptual/AppleScriptLangGuide/introduction/ASLR_intro.html">AppleScript</a> dan <a href="http://support.apple.com/en-us/ht2488">Automator</a> dirasa tak cukup untuk mengotomatisasi berbagi pekerjaan pada Mac maka JavaScript for Automation (JXA) boleh dicoba. <a href="https://twitter.com/The_Axx">Alex Guyot</a> melalui Macstories telah memberikan sedikit gambaran dan contoh bagaimana javascript dapat mendukung mempercepat workflow di OS X.</p>

<p>Let’s automate all the things!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Maestro Macro: Quoting a Website in Markdown — The Brooks Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/keyboard-maestro-quoting-a-website-in-markdown/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-24T22:27:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/keyboard-maestro-quoting-a-website-in-markdown</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>The benefit is that now I can select text on a page, hit the hot key and paste to my document, saving a bunch of extra clicks. It’s not the best, but it sped things up a touch for me.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Waini! Makin mudah lagi bikin postingan <em>linked list</em>. Tapi kalau pas kerja di Windows tetep aja kudu copy-paste manual.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
