<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Iphone | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/iphone/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-18T08:53:12+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone Extensions Trick]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-iphone-extensions-trick/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-16T11:22:32+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-iphone-extensions-trick</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a trick everyone should know.
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>When creating a contact, instead of this:</p></p><p><p>Jenny<br/>866-5309 x1982</p></p><p><p>Do this:</p></p><p><p>Jenny<br/>866-5309;1982</p></p><p><p>The semicolon is secret code to your iPhone to wait once the call connects and gives you the option to dial the extension when you tap it at the bottom of the screen.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life After Cancer: How the iPhone Helped Me Achieve a Healthier Lifestyle]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-04T07:46:22+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> wrote a story that everyone should read:</p>

<p><blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Since being diagnosed with Hodgkin Lymphoma (Stage IV) in late 2011, my life changed. Beyond the psychological and emotional consequences of how cancer affected me, my family, and my relationships, it is undeniable and abundantly clear that cancer took its toll on me from a physical perspective.</p></p><p><p>Last year, I decided to regain control of my body, my life habits, and my health. I started tracking everything I could about my activities, my exercise routine, the food I ate, and the time I spent working with my iPad instead of walking, sleeping, or enjoying time with my family. Since then, I’ve made a decision to not let cancer and its consequences define me any longer.</p></p><p><p>I want to be healthier, I want to eat better, and I want to take the second chance I was given and make the most of it. What started as an experiment has become a new daily commitment to improve my lifestyle and focus.</p></p><p><p>And it wouldn’t be possible without my iPhone.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Have you ever wondered how a product of a company could change people’s life? A good company not only built a product to make money but also built a product which can change people’s life. </p>

<p>Go, send <a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> writings on your favorite read-later service.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing Photo Metadata With Metapho — MacSparky]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/removing-photo-metadata-with-metapho/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-22T14:57:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/removing-photo-metadata-with-metapho</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="!g" title="twitter macsparky">David Sparks</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>The app is easy enough to use. Select an existing photo and push the big red button to remove the metadata.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Menghilangkan metadata dari sebuah foto kini menjadi mudah berkat <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/metapho-manage-photo-metadata/id914457352?ls=1&amp;mt=8?at=10laz7&amp;ct=blog">Metapho</a>. Bagi yang menaruh perhatian lebih terkait masalah keamanan atau privasi maka in-app-purchase seharga 2$ dalam aplikasi ini bukanlah sebuah masalah besar.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Better Way to Combine iPhone Screenshots With Keyboard Maestro]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/combine-apple-screenshot-using-keyboard-maestro/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-03T17:09:30+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/combine-apple-screenshot-using-keyboard-maestro</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> via <a href="http://www.macstories.net/">Macstories</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>This is one of my most-used Keyboard Maestro macros on a daily basis: it allows me to produce good-looking iPhone screenshots that fit better together with a single keystroke. It literally takes 2 seconds to complete, instead of the couple of minutes you would spend in Acorn or Photoshop to resize, paste, and align.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Menulis artikel tips dan trik untuk sebuah blog teknologi lokal terkadang dituntut adanya screenshot untuk mempermudah pemahaman dari topik yang sedang dibahas. Sebelumnya, untuk menggabungkan beberapa screenshot saya akan membuka Pixelmator dan menyusunnya. Hal ini tentu kurang efektif dan memakan waktu.</p>

<p>Hari ini saya gembira karena menemukan artikel mengenai penggunaan Keyboard Maestro untuk melakukan resize screenshot dari iPhone dan menggabungkannya. Jika biasanya saya menggunakan Pixelmator untuk mengedit dan menggabungkan screenshot memakan waktu lebih dari 15 menit maka dengan macro dari <a href="http://twitter.com/macdrifter">Gabe</a> yang dibahas oleh <a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> tersebut kini hanya perlu waktu kurang dari 5 detik.</p>

<p>Artikel diatas memang sudah cukup lumayan lama mengingat jika dilihat dari published date sudah lebih dari dua tahun berlalu, dan mungkin waktu itu saya masih asik hanya menonton film menggunakan Macbook White yang kini sudah pensiun. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple vs Jailbreak]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-01T23:03:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.apple.com/legal/sales-support/sales-policies/retail_us.html">Apple</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>Making unauthorized modifications to the software on an iPhone violates the iPhone software license agreement. The common term for modifying an iPhone is jail-breaking, with a particular emphasis on the second part of that term. That’s why we strongly, almost emphatically, recommend that you do not do so. Really. Should you be unable to use your iPhone due to an unauthorized software modification, its repair will not be covered under the warranty.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Apple memang sudah lama menentang ataupun tak mengijinkan penggunanya untuk melakukan jailbreak. Pada halaman <em>sales policy</em> di atas bahkan Apple tak bertanggung jawab atas kerusakan yang terjadi akibat modifikasi dari sistem operasi iOS dalam hal ini berarti hangusnya garansi perangkat.</p>

<!--more-->

<p>Keputusan untuk melakukan jailbreak memang sepenuhnya ada di tangan pengguna dan tak selamanya jailbreak berdampak buruk. Bagi seorang pengembang ataupun seseorang yang ingin mempelajari tentang sistem operasi terutama iOS, jailbreak bisa saja merupakan sebuah langkah untuk mendukung kegiatannya. Tak hanya itu, jailbreak yang membuka akses <em>root</em> perangkat juga memungkinkan pengguna untuk mengkustomisasi perangkat yang dimiliki mulai dari menginstall tema, mengubah ikon batere atau sinyal, menghilangkan UI yang dianggap mengganggu dan masih banyak lagi. Namun juga tak jarang beberapa orang melakukan jailbreak untuk mengunduh dan menginstall aplikasi bajakan yang tentu saja merugikan bagi pengembang aplikasi padahal banyak cara untuk mendapatkan sebuah aplikasi secara legal, memakai iTunes gift card misalnya.</p>

<p>Memang secara teori, jailbreak bisa dihilangkan cukup dengan melakukan restore perangkat menggunakan iTunes apabila ingin melakukan klaim garansi, namun jika terjadi hal yang tak diinginkan semisal <em>brick</em> pada perangkat karena tak sengaja melakukan <em>Reset All Settings</em> maka siapa yang akan bertanggung jawab? Oleh sebab itu mengapa jailbreak selalu disertai dengan <em>disclaimer</em>: DWYOR (Do With Your Own Risk)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
