<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: osx | Sweet Distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/osx/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-28T09:50:41+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Play a Power Charging Sound Effect in OS X When a MacBook is Plugged in (Like iOS)]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/play-sound-effect-in-osx-like-iOS/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-18T08:18:05+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/play-sound-effect-in-osx-like-iOS</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Seems interesting, let’s try!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hammerspoon]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-17T17:42:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you’re into workflow automation, then you might want to check this out. Hammerspoon is Lua based scripting engine for OS X. Just write the code in Lua language and it can interact with OS X APIs such as: clipboard, mouse pointers,filesystem objects, audio, batteries, and more.</p>

<p>If your nerdy side is kickin’ out then why not to try this?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Perspective]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-06T11:32:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/">Joe Cieplinski</a> write responses about Marco’s thought:
<blockquote><p>Almost two years ago, I suggested that Apple would be better off slowing down and taking a year off to fix bugs and enhance already existing features, rather than continue the fevered pace of innovation that it had maintained for so many years. Clearly, Tim Cook ignored my advice. And how could he not? After Jobs’ death, the world consistently questioned Cook’s ability to keep the company in its role as the richest, most powerful, and innovative tech company in the universe. He had a lot to prove. There were expectations that needed to be met, and so he met them.</p></p><p><p>Unfortunately, meeting those expectations has had consequences.</p></p><p><p>You can’t have it both ways. You can’t stay way ahead of the curve and not introduce some bugs along the way. This decline in software quality is a side-effect of the current strategy. It’s a compromise Apple has made in order to reassure the general public that the company isn’t “doomed” without Steve Jobs.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>And he put this before closing paragraph:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>The unfortunate reality is that “Here’s a new version that’s the same as the old version, except now everything works” is a tough sell.</p></blockquote></p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/balance/">Macstories</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>What it comes down to, really, is balance. I believe that Apple used to be more disciplined at balancing its desire for new features and commitment to refinements.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Sure, Apple has a lot of things in their to do list. As I wrote <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/that-goddamn-truth/">last night</a>, many new features will also bring a new bugs and maybe impact on stability. Does current Apple’s software quality decline? Yes it does. Does it just work like ever before? Yes but I’m not sure I’ll answer it wholeheartedly. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Goddamn Truth]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-05T22:12:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:
<blockquote><p>I suspect the rapid decline of Apple’s software is a sign that marketing is too high a priority at Apple today: having major new releases every year is clearly impossible for the engineering teams to keep up with while maintaining quality. Maybe it’s an engineering problem, but I suspect not — I doubt that any cohesive engineering team could keep up with these demands and maintain significantly higher quality.</p></p><p><p>The problem seems to be quite simple: they’re doing too much, with unrealistic deadlines.</p></p><p><p>We don’t need major OS releases every year. We don’t need each OS release to have a huge list of new features. We need our computers, phones, and tablets to work well first so we can enjoy new features released at a healthy, gradual, sustainable pace.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>That goddamn truth! I don’t deny that iOS and OS X are rapidly growing over these 2 years. Many features and improvements they put at their software but it also increase the bugs, crashes and inconsistency. So many things are broken and need to be fixed. At least they need to slow down the software upgrade cycle and start to fix everything they broke.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe life into an old Mac — 512 Pixels]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/breathe-life-into-old-mac/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-01T22:49:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/breathe-life-into-old-mac</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Joe Caiati menulis di <a href="http://www.512pixels.net">512 Pixels</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Luckily, older Macs are more flexible with hardware upgrades and coupled with third-party software, you can unlock features that Apple doesn’t support on older models. Here is how to get the most life out of an aging Mac.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Perangkat Mac memang tak terbilang murah, untuk itulah pengguna harus pintar-pintar mencari cara bagaimana agar Mac yang telah lama dimiliki tetap memiliki performa yang baik. Biasanya, Mac versi lama memiliki beberapa komponen yang dapat diupgrade sendiri oleh pemiliknya dan mengganti RAM atau hard drive dengan spesifikasi yang lebih baik bisa menjadi alternatif untuk mengembalikan performa Mac yang dirasa sudah mulai menurun.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
