<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-12T20:25:13+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Chaining Things and iOS Reminders with IFTTT]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/Chaining-Things-and-iOS-Reminders-with-IFTTT/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-04-12T19:29:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/Chaining-Things-and-iOS-Reminders-with-IFTTT</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GTD or <a href="http://gettingthingsdone.com">Getting Things Done®</a> is a stress free productivity technique based on David Allen which is awesome and many of the nerds talk about it. It’s simply take 5 steps to GTD: capture, clarify, organize, reflect and engage. Sounds easy, huh?</p>

<p>I knew it last year. Since then I tried to get many references and tools to support GTD systems. I still failed. Sometimes I still fall into cracks, sometimes I let my lists outdated, and the next week I rebuild it.</p>

<p>I’ve tried <a href="https://www.omnigroup.com/omnifocus">Omnifocus</a>, plain text based <a href="http://www.hogbaysoftware.com/products/taskpaper">Taskpaper</a>, Things for my task management system to implement GTD and the last one is my choice. <a href="http://culturedcode.com">Cultured Code</a> the developer behind Things make a great software even the development pace is too slow according to some people.</p>

<p>I love using Things because of its simplicity. The syncing is also fast and reliable. The ease of using Things is there’s no learning curve instead of GTD itself. I don’t said that Omnifocus isn’t a great tools but I get myself overwhelm everytime I open Omnifocus and try to use it. </p>

<p>One features that makes me envy as Things user from Omnifocus is MailDrop features which you can use to send a task to your inbox just by emailing it. Why I envy this features is the fact that I have to use PC at work and there’s such Things for Windows to easily put the task in. </p>

<p>Luckily there’s service called <a href="https://ifttt.com">IFTTT</a> which we can use to mimic Omnifocus’ Maildrop features. Things have Reminders integrations which can import all the task in the reminder to its inbox. Now all you have to do is just set up a email trigger in IFTTT that would add a body email as a task with preferred tags in subjects to iOS Reminders. I have Things list in my iOS Reminders that Things ready to import. So, all I need is to set up a recipe that will be triggered by an email with #thingstodo as tag in subjects and a task which I want to add in Things in body email. You can get the IFTTT recipe <a href="https://ifttt.com/recipes/278606-thingstodo-email-to-ios-reminders">here</a>.</p>

<p>Now wherever something pops out in my mind while I’m working at work, I just compose email with that tags and send them. At lunch, I will open Things and the list is ready to import. </p>

<p>Sometimes, the recipes don’t start automatically and I have to open IF apps but at least, I become worry less to forget what’s important during works.</p>

]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Cook on Apple's Future: Everything Can Change Except Values ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.fastcompany.com/3042435/steves-legacy-tim-looks-ahead"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-03-28T16:21:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/fast-company-tim-cook-interview</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tim Cook on <a href="http://www.fastcompany.com/3042435/steves-legacy-tim-looks-ahead">FastCompany</a> interview:</p>
<blockquote><p>There’s this thing in technology, almost a disease, where the definition of success is making the most. How many clicks did you get, how many active users do you have, how many units did you sell? Everybody in technology seems to want big numbers. Steve never got carried away with that. He focused on making the best.</p></blockquote>

<p>GOLD!</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/fast-company-tim-cook-interview/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 8 Changed How I Work on My iPhone and iPad  ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/ios-8-changed-how-i-work-on-my-iphone-and-ipad/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-03-17T07:42:30+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iOS8-stories</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> thought about iOS 8 and bunch of its features last year on Macstories:</p>
<blockquote><p>What I realized in using extensions is how necessary last year&#8217;s redesign of iOS was. Imagine if Apple didn&#8217;t ship a new design with iOS 7: today, we&#8217;d have sheets of stitched leather or shiny metal on top of apps that look like agendas or little robots. The cohesiveness and subdued style that iOS 7 brought with its precise structure and hierarchy allows extensions to integrate nicely with apps, feeling like extra actions rather than eerily realistic objects.
<br />
<br />The impact of action and share extensions on my workflow has been massive even with only a few apps and bugs left in iOS 8. I use my iPad more because I spend less time switching between apps, copying text around, or moving files between different containers. I&#8217;m more efficient thanks to extensions because the quality of the software I use every day has increased considerably. I can&#8217;t imagine what we&#8217;ll start seeing today with action and share extensions on the App Store.</p></blockquote>

<p>When iOS 7 came out, I didn’t satisfy with the new UI. I wished there’s a way to downgrade back to iOS 6. The main reason was the unbearable lagging and blindly white all over iOS for that time. Then iOS 8 came out last year, I upgraded. Now when I look at iOS today, I would think many times to downgrade even when there’s a way to do. </p>

<p>Extensions, change how we used iOS. I could easily post to Tumblr, Path, Twitter. I could easily find a inspiring quote, make selection and save it on my Notes folder in Dropbox that also available on my nvAlt. 3rd party keyboard, let us manage multiple clipboard like <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/en/app/clips-copy-paste-anywhere/id917638056?mt=8">Clips</a> does. Finding the right emoji, now become easier, there’s <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/emoji++-fast-emoji-keyboard/id919234935?mt=8">Emoji++</a>.</p>

<p>And if I look back to iOS 6 (yeah, my friends still use iOS 6.1.3 in her iPhone 4s), it look dull and outdated.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iOS8-stories/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[TextExpander Mass Snippets Generator]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/text-expander-mass-snippets-generator.markdown/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-03-04T22:51:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/text-expander-mass-snippets-generator.markdown</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/bekerja-multi-platform-mac-windows">Working multi-platform</a> operating systems Windows and Mac sometimes give you pain in the ass. You can do something easily on Mac but maybe not in Windows and vice versa. Overmore, I’ve to work in Windows machine with limited user previlege so I can’t install any software I want. </p>

<p>If you know what apps that I miss when working in Windows, I would gladly say it’s TextExpander. I feel I could do anything with with <a href="http://smilesoftware.com/TextExpander/index.html">TextExpander</a> on my Mac but when it comes to work with my lovely Windows machine, I feel odd. Luckily I found a similar apps, <a href="www.phraseexpress.com">PhraseExpress</a>. 
<!--more--></p>

<p>I’m working with thousand files on the network storage at office. The pain is when I’ve to move from a folder to another folder and imagine when you’ve to dig into 4 nested folder to get the files, how many mouse clicks and scroll you need? So I want to make a snippets that expand into a directory address and simulating <code>Enter</code> key so I automatically jump to the destination folder. Luckily I found this <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/2013/01/04/mass-creating-textexpander-snippets/">blog post</a> by Brett Terpstra. </p>

<p>I’ve been long reader of <a href="http://twitter.com/ttscoff">@ttscoff</a> blog. I use some of his projects, nvAlt, <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/projects/bretts-popclip-extensions/">PopClip extensions</a>, <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/projects/searchlink/">SearchLink</a>and his crazy <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/projects/keybindings/">keybindings</a>. So after reading his blog post, I fired up MS Excel and make the .csv files as suggested. The script ran very well and it took less than a 30 seconds to make almost 300 snippets on my CSV file, really a time saver.</p>

<p>I modified the script a bit to put the label for the snippets that would be created. On the .CSV file, put the label on the third row. </p>

<p>Here’s the modified version:</p>
<div><script src="https://gist.github.com/d51fd7fc137c4951686a.js?file=textexpander_gen.rb"></script>
<noscript><pre><code>#!/usr/bin/ruby
require &#39;csv&#39;
require &#39;erb&#39;
require &#39;cgi&#39;

if ARGV.length == 2
	input_csv = ARGV[0]
	output_te = ARGV[1]
	unless output_te =~ /\.textexpander$/
		puts &quot;Second argument must have a &#39;.textexpander&#39; extension.&quot;
		puts &quot;#{File.basename(__FILE__)} input.csv output[.textexpander]&quot;
		exit
	end
else
	puts &quot;Two arguments are required, input filename and output filename&quot;
	puts &quot;#{ARGV[0]} input.csv output[.textexpander]&quot;
	exit
end

template = ERB.new &lt;&lt;-ENDTEMPLATE
		&lt;dict&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;abbreviation&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;string&gt;&lt;%= abbr %&gt;&lt;/string&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;abbreviationMode&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;integer&gt;0&lt;/integer&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;creationDate&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;date&gt;2013-01-03T20:17:10Z&lt;/date&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;flags&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;integer&gt;0&lt;/integer&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;label&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;string&gt;&lt;%= label %&gt;&lt;/string&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;modificationDate&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;date&gt;2013-01-03T20:19:04Z&lt;/date&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;plainText&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;string&gt;&lt;%= expansion %&gt;&lt;/string&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;snippetType&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;integer&gt;0&lt;/integer&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;useCount&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;integer&gt;0&lt;/integer&gt;
			&lt;key&gt;uuidString&lt;/key&gt;
			&lt;string&gt;&lt;%= uuid %&gt;&lt;/string&gt;
		&lt;/dict&gt;
ENDTEMPLATE

header =&lt;&lt;-ENDHEADER
&lt;?xml version=&quot;1.0&quot; encoding=&quot;UTF-8&quot;?&gt;
&lt;!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC &quot;-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN&quot; &quot;http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd&quot;&gt;
&lt;plist version=&quot;1.0&quot;&gt;
&lt;dict&gt;
	&lt;key&gt;groupInfo&lt;/key&gt;
	&lt;dict&gt;
		&lt;key&gt;expandAfterMode&lt;/key&gt;
		&lt;integer&gt;2&lt;/integer&gt;
		&lt;key&gt;groupName&lt;/key&gt;
		&lt;string&gt;#{File.basename(output_te).gsub(/\.textexpander$/,&#39;&#39;)}&lt;/string&gt;
	&lt;/dict&gt;
	&lt;key&gt;snippetsTE2&lt;/key&gt;
	&lt;array&gt;
ENDHEADER

footer =&lt;&lt;-ENDFOOTER
	&lt;/array&gt;
&lt;/dict&gt;
&lt;/plist&gt;
ENDFOOTER

fh = File.new(File.expand_path(output_te),&#39;w+&#39;)
input = CSV.read(File.expand_path(input_csv))

fh.puts header

input.each { |item|
	abbr = CGI.escapeHTML(item[0].strip)
	expansion = CGI.escapeHTML(item[1].strip)
	label = CGI.escapeHTML(item[2].strip)
	uuid = %x{uuidgen}.strip
	$stderr.puts &quot;Processed #{abbr} -&gt; #{expansion}&quot;
	fh.puts template.result(binding)
}

fh.puts footer
fh.close
</code></pre></noscript></div>

<p>The original version of this script can be found on the <a href="http://twitter.com/ttscoff">@ttscoff</a>’s <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/2013/01/04/mass-creating-textexpander-snippets/">blog</a>. This is real time-saver. Thanks, Brett! </p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Life After Cancer: How the iPhone Helped Me Achieve a Healthier Lifestyle ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/life-after-cancer-how-the-iphone-helped-me-achieve-a-healthier-lifestyle/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-03-04T07:46:22+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> wrote a story that everyone should read:</p>

<blockquote><p>Since being diagnosed with Hodgkin Lymphoma (Stage IV) in late 2011, my life changed. Beyond the psychological and emotional consequences of how cancer affected me, my family, and my relationships, it is undeniable and abundantly clear that cancer took its toll on me from a physical perspective.
<br />
<br />Last year, I decided to regain control of my body, my life habits, and my health. I started tracking everything I could about my activities, my exercise routine, the food I ate, and the time I spent working with my iPad instead of walking, sleeping, or enjoying time with my family. Since then, I&#8217;ve made a decision to not let cancer and its consequences define me any longer.
<br />
<br />I want to be healthier, I want to eat better, and I want to take the second chance I was given and make the most of it. What started as an experiment has become a new daily commitment to improve my lifestyle and focus.
<br />
<br />And it wouldn&#8217;t be possible without my iPhone.</p></blockquote>

<p>Have you ever wondered how a product of a company could change people’s life? A good company not only built a product to make money but also built a product which can change people’s life. </p>

<p>Go, send <a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> writings on your favorite read-later service.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Workflow 1.1: Deeper iOS Automation ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macstories.net/reviews/workflow-1-1-deeper-ios-automation/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-03-03T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/workflow-iOS-automation</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="www.macstories.net">MacStories</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>In a few months (I first started testing Workflow in August 2014), Workflow has become an essential component of how I get work done on iOS. The improvements and features launched today extend the app&#8217;s capabilities deeper into native iOS frameworks – whether you want to find photos, filter files and calendar events, or save selections from Safari, Workflow is becoming a command center for iOS that can do anything. It&#8217;s powerful, and there are still a few issues to fix, but it&#8217;s useful, and, even better, it&#8217;s fun.</p></blockquote>

<p>I’ve tweeted about Workflow several time and if you need a good place to start then look no further. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/workflow-iOS-automation/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Pricing of Apple Watch ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://daringfireball.net/2015/02/apple_watch_pricing"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-02-21T08:42:36+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-watch-pricing</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting thought of<a href="https://twitter.com/gruber">John Gruber</a> about Apple Watch pricing: </p>
<blockquote><p>Apple Watch Edition is not a tech product, so don’t try to price it like one.</p></blockquote>

<p>I love the footnote of his post: </p>

<blockquote><p>At prices like these, an Apple Watch Edition is not an accessory for your iPhone — your iPhone is an accessory for your Apple Watch Edition.</p></blockquote>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-watch-pricing/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Hammerspoon ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.hammerspoon.org/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-02-17T17:42:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you’re into workflow automation, then you might want to check this out. Hammerspoon is Lua based scripting engine for OS X. Just write the code in Lua language and it can interact with OS X APIs such as: clipboard, mouse pointers,filesystem objects, audio, batteries, and more.</p>

<p>If your nerdy side is kickin’ out then why not to try this?</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/hammerspoon/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Pale Blue Dot ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.php?feature=4484"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-02-17T11:07:58+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/pale-blue-dot</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/palebluedot.jpg" /></p>

<p>Forget about Valentine Days. On February 14, 1990 <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Voyager_1">NASA’s Voyager Spacecraft</a> capture a photo of our solar system. The photo includes Neptune, Uranus, Jupiter, Venus and Earth-which showed up as pale blue dot in the brown light that resembles a beam of sunlight. This year, the photo is turned 25 years old.</p>

<p>The photo was taken when Voyager 1 was 40 astronomical units from the sun which is equivalent to 6000 million kilometers. </p>

<p>Carl Sagan wrote in his “Pale Blue Dot” book: </p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;That&#8217;s here. That&#8217;s home. That&#8217;s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. &#8230; There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world.&#8221;</p></blockquote>

<p>This photo is kinda a reminder that with all of our passion, all of our love, lucks and sucks, all of our dreams and shits we still isn’t bigger than a dust or even a pixel.</p>

<p>It’s good to be reminded this way once in a while. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/pale-blue-dot/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Tim Cook at the Goldman Sachs Conference ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.imore.com/tim-cook-goldman-sachs-conference"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-02-12T09:25:04+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/settern">Serenity Caldwell</a> made a transcipt for iMore about Tim Cook talks at the Goldman Sachs Conferences. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[The Reason You Should Draft Your Blog Posts Outside WordPress ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://john.do/draft/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-02-03T08:04:53+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/drafts-wordpress</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://john.do">John Saddington</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The point is this: The reason you draft outside of WordPress is because there’s less of a chance of losing your hard work!</p></blockquote>

<p>That’s true! Goddamn true! </p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/drafts-wordpress/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[If Apple Made Milk ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/if-apple-made-milk-and-other-super-cool-imaginary-product-packaging-162398"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-27T09:15:44+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What if Apple and others popular brand do packaging to your daily needs at grocery?</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Favorite App For Shared Lists ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://thesweetsetup.com/apps/favorite-app-shared-lists/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-23T10:35:52+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/favorite-shared-list-apps</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Available in all platform even as browser extensions, syncs pretty well, can add subtask and attach PDF, media, link, easy sharing with others. Well, no wonder they pick Wunderlist. </p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/favorite-shared-list-apps/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Ever Use This Listed Password ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macrumors.com/2015/01/20/123456-2014-worst-password-of-the-year/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-22T10:58:39+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/don&#8217;t-use-this-password</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Really, people still use <code>123456</code> as their password in 2014? <em>sigh</em></p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/don't-use-this-password/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Custom Function in Google Sheets ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.tech-recipes.com/rx/52659/google-sheets-how-to-write-a-custom-function/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-20T09:53:39+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/google-sheets-custom-functions</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nice tips how you can write functions using JavaScript in Google Sheets.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/google-sheets-custom-functions/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Small screen productivity ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://mattgemmell.com/small-screen-productivity/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T11:38:33+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/small-screen-produtivity</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/mattgemmell">Matt Gemmell</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>There’s something comforting about large screens; I’m well aware of that, and I feel it too. The expanse of screen-space hints at creative possibilities. You probably wouldn’t want to do full-time graphics work or app development without a large and/or additional screen, either. You can, but those are specialised disciplines where you can make a strong argument for two-up or even larger displays.
<br />
<br /> For the vast bulk of stuff that most people will want to do on a computer, though, most of the time you don’t need a desktop monster. I don’t think you even need a 15” screen, which is essentially a portable desktop. You just have to use a small screen productively.</p></blockquote>

<p>Dear Macbook Air user, you should read this.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/small-screen-produtivity/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Monument Valley in Numbers ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://blog.monumentvalleygame.com/blog/2015/1/15/monument-valley-in-numbers"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T10:34:18+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Take a look at the statistic and how the revenue from iOS almost dominate all the revenue they get. Also remember that only 40% iOS user <a href="https://twitter.com/ustwogames/status/552136427904184320">paid for the game</a>.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Things for iPhone and iPad updated with new Notification Center widget ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2015/01/15/things-todo-nc-widget/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T07:57:08+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Via <a href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/">iDownloadblog</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Popular task managing app Things pushed out an update to its iPhone and iPad clients today, bringing both apps to version 2.6. The symmetrical updates bring improvements to the URI scheme, for better inter-app communication, and a new Notification Center Widget.</p></blockquote>

<p>Update! Update! I love Things than the other popular task management apps. Its simplicity and easy to use is one of main reason I choose Things. This update makes easier to glance at what you’ve to do through Notification Center. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned and Reimagined Macintosh ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://curved.de/news/curvedlabs-ein-facelift-fuer-den-macintosh-198570"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-14T09:39:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/redesigned-and-reimagined-macintosh</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/macintosh.jpg" /></p>

<p>What if the original Macintosh is getting redesigned? Maybe this rendering is the answer but from its thinness it looks like a docked iPad, IMHO. Anyway, I love the space gray color.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/redesigned-and-reimagined-macintosh/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[A Teenager’s View on Social Media ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://medium.com/backchannel/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media-1df945c09ac6"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-12T08:46:27+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Those are some reasons why many people my age tend to use Instagram more than they do Facebook. Everything about the application makes it less commercialized and more focused on the content, meaning more teens are inclined to visit it. When we do visit the application it is a much more pleasant experience so we are more inclined to Like and interact with the posts more. This increases our interaction with the application, meaning we will use it more, etc.</p></blockquote>

<p>A very nice read about how social media nowadays change how people are reached by each others, but still as my parents said, making call is still the easiest one.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  </feed>