<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-12-02T22:58:25+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stunning Markdown and Writing App for Mac — Typed ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://realmacsoftware.com/typed"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-02T21:19:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/realmacsoftware-release-typed-text-editor</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="www.realmacsoftware.com">Realmac Software</a>:</p>

<blockquote><h2>Your Best Work Isn’t Written, It’s Typed.</h2>

<p>Typed is the stunning new writing app for the Mac, and the first that improves your focus so you can create great content. Typed makes writing for the web incredibly easy, and its Zen Mode features relaxing soundtracks that help you concentrate.</p></blockquote>

<p>Realmac Software yang juga pengembang dari aplikasi dari <a href="http://realmacsoftware.com/clear">Clear</a>, <a href="http://realmacsoftware.com/ember">Ember</a>, <a href="http://realmacsoftware.com/rapidweaver">Rapidweaver</a> baru saja merilis aplikasi berupa teks editor yang diberi nama <a href="http://realmacsoftware.com/typed">Typed</a>.</p>

<p>Sama dengan teks editor yang lain seperti <a href="http://bywordapp.com">Byword</a> dan <a href="http://www.iawriter.com/mac/">iA Writer</a>, Typed mendukung penulisan dengan menggunakan <a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/">markdown</a>. Typed juga menyediakan fitur kustomisasi tampilan seperti skema warna aplikasi atau tema dan font yang digunakan. Salah satu yang menarik dari Typed adalah adanya fitur Zen mode dimana pengguna akan ditemani oleh sebuah soundtracks yang menenangkan sehingga pengguna bisa lebih fokus dengan apa yang sedang ditulisnya.</p>

<p>Penghitung kata, fitur export tulisan ke format HTML, RTF, keyboard shortcuts, auto save support merupakan beberapa fitur yang dihadirkan Realmac Software di Typed. Dirilis dengan harga $19,99 untuk waktu yang terbatas (harga asli $24.99), Typed memang lebih mahal daripada beberapa teks editor lain seperti Byword ($9.99) dan iA Writer ($9.99). Namun jangan khawati karena Realmac Software menyediakan trial aplikasinya selama 7 hari bagi pengguna sebelum membelinya. Saya sudah mencobanya dengan menuliskan artikel ini.  Terdapat efek blur pada latar belakang teks editor Typed selaras dengan OS X Yosemite ketika sedang digunakan dan saya sendiri kurang menyukainya karena bisa saja menimbulkan distraksi.</p>

<p>Semakin banyak aplikasi berjenis teks editor yang dirilis di platform Mac. Dengan gimmick berupa fitur zen mode dimana Typed menyediakan soundtrack sebagai teman menulis, rasanya berkompromi dengan harga yang ditawarkan masih bisa dimaklumi.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/realmacsoftware-release-typed-text-editor/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps cannot use Push Notifications to send promotions, unless you’re Apple or anyone else ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.marco.org/2014/12/01/app-store-rule-5-6"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-02T10:20:38+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>If Apple won’t enforce its own standards against spamming and annoying customers — which really isn’t good enough — the least they can do is practice the rules themselves and be a good example.</p></blockquote>


<p>Maybe Apple just being consistent to what its CEO said back to WWDC this year: &ldquo;This is something only Apple could do.&rdquo;</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple VS Jailbreak]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-01T23:03:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.apple.com/legal/sales-support/sales-policies/retail_us.html">Apple</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>Making unauthorized modifications to the software on an iPhone violates the iPhone software license agreement. The common term for modifying an iPhone is jail-breaking, with a particular emphasis on the second part of that term. That’s why we strongly, almost emphatically, recommend that you do not do so. Really. Should you be unable to use your iPhone due to an unauthorized software modification, its repair will not be covered under the warranty.</p></blockquote>


<p>Apple memang sudah lama menentang ataupun tak mengijinkan penggunanya untuk melakukan jailbreak. Pada halaman <em>sales policy</em> di atas bahkan Apple tak bertanggung jawab atas kerusakan yang terjadi akibat modifikasi dari sistem operasi iOS dalam hal ini berarti hangusnya garansi perangkat.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Keputusan untuk melakukan jailbreak memang sepenuhnya ada di tangan pengguna dan tak selamanya jailbreak berdampak buruk. Bagi seorang pengembang ataupun seseorang yang ingin mempelajari tentang sistem operasi terutama iOS, jailbreak bisa saja merupakan sebuah langkah untuk mendukung kegiatannya. Tak hanya itu, jailbreak yang membuka akses <em>root</em> perangkat juga memungkinkan pengguna untuk mengkustomisasi perangkat yang dimiliki mulai dari menginstall tema, mengubah ikon batere atau sinyal, menghilangkan UI yang dianggap mengganggu dan masih banyak lagi. Namun juga tak jarang beberapa orang melakukan jailbreak untuk mengunduh dan menginstall aplikasi bajakan yang tentu saja merugikan bagi pengembang aplikasi padahal banyak cara untuk mendapatkan sebuah aplikasi secara legal, memakai iTunes gift card misalnya.</p>

<p>Memang secara teori, jailbreak bisa dihilangkan cukup dengan melakukan restore perangkat menggunakan iTunes apabila ingin melakukan klaim garansi, namun jika terjadi hal yang tak diinginkan semisal <em>brick</em> pada perangkat karena tak sengaja melakukan <em>Reset All Settings</em> maka siapa yang akan bertanggung jawab? Oleh sebab itu mengapa jailbreak selalu disertai dengan <em>disclaimer</em>: DWYOR (Do With Your Own Risk)</p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[THE NEW 1WRITER WITH JAVASCRIPT ACTIONS ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://onetapless.com/new-1writer-with-javascript-actions"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-01T14:44:17+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-new-1writer-javascript-actions</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/pgruneich">Philip Gruneich</a> di <a href="http://onetapless.com">OneTapLess</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>1Writer 2.0 was the most delightful surprise this week and probably the best deal you could make this holiday if you write in your iOS devices. I’m sure it is only a matter of time until more actions pop up and improve the pool of options in this outstanding text editor.</p></blockquote>


<p><a href="http://1writerapp.com/">1Writer</a>, salah satu teks editor di iOS baru saja menerima pembaharuan besar. Penambahan <em>javascript action</em>, pengamanan tambahan dengan Touch ID, kustomisasi font serta tampilan, safari extensions, in-app-browser serta <em>today widget</em> untuk mengakses dokumen favorit secara cepat dan masih banyak lagi.</p>

<p>Ngoc Luu juga menambahkan <em><a href="http://1writerapp.com/actiondir">action directory</a></em> bagi pengguna yang ingin menambahkan <em>javascript action</em> dengan mudah ke dalam aplikasi 1Writer. Tak hanya itu, bagi pengguna yang ingin belajar membuat <em>javascript action</em> sendiri, Ngoc Luu juga sudah menyiapkan <a href="http://1writerapp.com/docs/js">dokumen</a> pendukung yang dapat dipelajari dan digunakan.</p>

<p>Seperti biasa, Philip Gruneich juga telah membuat artikel mengenai update dari 1Writer di OneTapLess dengan contoh <em>javascript action-nya</em>.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-new-1writer-javascript-actions/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[This app lets you unlock your Mac with Touch ID ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.cultofmac.com/304657/app-lets-unlock-mac-touch-id/#lEEV8APZLY4XDo8z.99"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-01T13:13:47+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unlock-macbook-with-touch-id</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Via <a href="www.cultofmac.com">CultofMac</a></p>

<blockquote><p>Called FingerKey, this new utility works by using Bluetooth 4.0 (what else?) to pair with your Mac, then forms a low latency, low energy wireless connection with an extra layer of 256-bit AES encryption on top to keep things secure.<br/><br/>Once you’ve got things paired, unlocking your Mac is as simple as getting into Bluetooth range, opening up the app, and putting your finger against the home button. There’s also a Notification Center Widget that makes things even easier, and FingerKey can actually unlock multiple Macs at a time.</p></blockquote>


<p>Macbook dengan Touch ID bisa saja menjadi inovasi Apple selanjutnya, namun sebelum itu terjadi kini membuka Mac dengan Touch ID yang terdapat di iPhone sudah bisa dilakukan.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unlock-macbook-with-touch-id/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[iClarified - Apple News - Jailbreak of iOS 8.1.1 and iOS 8.2 Beta Released! ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://m.iclarified.com/entry/index.php?enid=45676"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-29T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/ios-8.1.1-jailbreak-release</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Dari <a href="http://iclarified.com">iClarified</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>MuscleNerd confirmed the jailbreak over Twitter; however, he warns that you should probably wait a couple days before attempting.</p><p><br/>&#8220;Looks like TaiG just released a jailbreak for 8.1.1 (and 8.0,8.1,8.2beta). Best to wait a few days just in case&#8221;</p><p><br/>TaiG was part of the controversial iOS 7 jailbreak from the Evad3rs. The jaibreak included the TaiG &#8216;app store&#8217; for cracked apps by default in China.</p></blockquote>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/ios-8.1.1-jailbreak-release/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[How Apple keeps AirDrop files private and secure | iMore ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://m.imore.com/how-apple-keeps-your-airdrop-files-private-and-secure"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-29T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/how-apple-keeps-airdrop-files</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/reneritchie">Rene Ritchie</a> di iMore:</p>

<blockquote><h2>Encrypted identities</h2>

<p>When AirDrop is turned on, a 2048-bit RSA Identity is created and stored on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac. A hash, based on the phone numbers and/or email addresses associated with your Apple ID, is also created. That&rsquo;ll be used later to identify you in a way that maintains your privacy and security.</p></blockquote>

<p>Security! Security!</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/how-apple-keeps-airdrop-files/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[WatchBoard: a new Apple Watch SpringBoard replacement for iPhone and iPad ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2014/11/26/watchboard-apple-watch-iphone-ipad/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-28T17:31:38+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/watchboar-apple-watch-springboard-iphone-ipad</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Jeff Benjamin di <a href="www.idownloadblog.com.">iDownloadblog</a></p>

<blockquote><p>The thing I really like about WatchBoard is that no resprings are required when enabling or disabling the tweak. Yes, even when you want to fully replace the iPhone’s SpringBoard with the Apple Watch UI, no resprings are required, which is one of the best features of WatchBoard.</p></blockquote>

<p>Jika beberapa waktu sebelumnya Aeternum hadir sebagai jailbreak tweak yang membawa Apple Watch UI ke springboard iPhone atau iPad maka kini giliran WatchBoard dari Aaron Ash yang juga pencipta dari jailbreak tweak ternama, <a href="http://cydia.saurik.com/package/com.aaronash.barrel/">Barrel</a>.</p>

<p>Salah satu kekurangan dari Apple Watch UI di iPhone atau iPad adalah bagaimana dengan cepat membuka sebuah aplikasi yang diinginkan (saya memakai Aeternum dan hal ini juga menjadi salah satu masalah dalam menggunakan Apple Watch UI di keseharian). Namun jangan khawatir karena WatchBoard memiliki fitur untuk mengaktfikan spotlight dengan mudah, caranya tinggal tap di tempat yang kosong.</p>

<p>Ditawarkan dengan sedikit lebih mahal yaitu $3.99 dengan <a href="http://cydia.saurik.com/package/com.spiritoflogic.aeternum/">Aeternum</a>, WatchBoard mungkin dapat menjadi pilihan bagi yang tak sabar untuk mencoba Apple Watch UI di iPhone atau iPadnya.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/watchboar-apple-watch-springboard-iphone-ipad/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Site Generators ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://staticsitegenerators.net/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-28T10:37:54+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/static-site-generators</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bingung mau ngeblog pakai apa? Males daftar-daftar di Wordpress, Blogger, Tumblr? Situs yang satu ini punya daftar yang panjang tentang blog statis! Choose your own story lane to start.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/static-site-generators/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[#MacStoriesDeals Black Friday 2014: Best Deals for iPhone, iPad, and Mac Apps & Games ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macstories.net/roundups/macstoriesdeals-black-friday-2014-best-deals-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac-apps-games/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-27T09:14:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://macstories.net">Macstories</a></p>

<blockquote><p>Black Friday is upon us once again! #MacStoriesDeals is the best place to find great deals for iOS apps and games, Mac software, and more.</p></blockquote>

<p>Macstories telah merangkum beberapa deals diskon aplikasi baik untuk iPhone, iPad hingga Mac menjelang Black Friday.</p>

<p>Fantastical 2 yang menjadi aplikasi kalender favorit saya juga ada dalam daftar, kini hanya $1.99 untuk iPhone dan $4.99 untuk iPad serta $9.99 untuk Mac. Jika belum yakin untuk mencoba Fantastical 2 maka sebaiknya baca dulu <a href="http://www.macstories.net/reviews/fantastical-2-review/">review</a> dari Macstories.</p>

<p>Selain deals di atas, <a href="http://smilesoftware.com/TextExpander/touch/index.html">Text Expander Touch</a> menjadi Rp. 12 Ribu di App Store Indonesia. Namun ketika saya membuka App Store US, harga dari Text Expander Touch masih sama yaitu $4.99.</p>

<p>So, stay update!</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone - Blackberry Trade Up Offer ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://tradeup.blackberry.com/en/us/web/passport.html"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-26T01:37:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iphone-blackberry-trade-up-program</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Blackberry di situsnya:</p>

<blockquote><p>Trade your iPhone for a BlackBerry Passport and get up to $550!</p>

<p>For a limited time, starting December 1st.</p>

<p>Upgrade to a BlackBerry® Passport and get up to $400 back for your iPhone and an additional $150 from BlackBerry.</p></blockquote>

<p>Ada yang mau tukar iPhone 6-nya sama Blackberry Passport?</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iphone-blackberry-trade-up-program/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Unread for iPad relaunches as a freemium app ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2014/11/25/unread-for-ipad-relaunches-as-a-freemium-app/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-26T01:33:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unread-ipad-jadi-freemium</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Dari iDownloadblog:</p>

<blockquote><p>Previously costing five bucks a pop, Unread for iPad is now a free download with In-App Purchases to unlock advanced features. The app sports full-screen reading, has multiple themes for day, night and some such, features rich content sharing via OvershareKit and much more.</p></blockquote>

<p>Sayang udah ngga punya iPad lagi, ada yang mau kasih?</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unread-ipad-jadi-freemium/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[San Fransisco Sebagai System Font di iOS]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/san-fransisco-ios-fonts/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-25T22:08:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/san-fransisco-ios-fonts</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/settingcomparison.png" title="Settings" ></p>

<p>Sejak Apple mengumumkan Apple Watch SDK, San Fransisco, font yang dibuat Apple secara khusus yang menjadi default font di Apple Watch mulai menjadi perbincangan. Bahkan beberapa orang sudah memportingnya untuk dapat dipakai di <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/san-fransisco-yosemite-font/">Mac</a>.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/notescomparison.png" title="Notes" >
Bagi yang melakukan jailbreak maka font San Fransisco kini dapat dinikmati sebagai system font di perangkat iOS. <a href="https://twitter.com/dbk1ng">Daniel B. King</a>, memporting font ini agar dapat digunakan di perangkat iOS. Caranya mudah, cukup install aplikasi Bytafont2 dari Cydia dan unduh San Fransisco font dari repo <code>http://dbk1ng.myrepospace.com</code>. Setelah itu, pilih San Fransisco yang ada di daftar font pada aplikasi Bytafont2 dan perangkat akan secara otomatis respring. Saya sendiri lebih menyukain San Fransisco daripada Helvetica Neue meski baru sebentar menggunakannya. Mungkin saja nantinya Apple berencana mengganti system font iOS 9 ke San Fransisco.</p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[30 Tahun Setelah Apple Macintosh Pertama Dirilis ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://thingsofinterest.com/2014/10/22/difference-30-years-makes-imac-retina-5k-display-vs-original-macintosh/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-25T08:26:53+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/30-tahun-setelah-apple-macintosh-pertama-dirilis</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Kent Akgungor di <a href="http://thingsofinterest.com/">Things Of Interest</a></p>

<blockquote><p>When first released in 1984, the Apple Macintosh shipped with a black-and-white 512 x 342 display. Fast forward 30 years to the release of the iMac with Retina 5K display, which ships with a 5,120 x 2,880 display with support for millions of colours. That’s an increase from 175,000 pixels to more than 14.7 million – an 8,400% increase. 80 of the original Macintosh displays fit within a single Retina 5K display.</p></blockquote>

<p>It&rsquo;s terrific what Apple could&rsquo;ve done in 30 years and still counting.</p>

<p>Mike Salomon di <a href="http://www.thecleverest.com/">The Cleverest</a> mencoba melakukan hal sebaliknya.</p>

<blockquote><p>So I thought I’d take the opposite approach. Below are 1-to-1 pixel mockups of how Mac OSX Yosemite would have appeared on the original Macintosh’s 512×342 pixel screen.</p></blockquote>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/30-tahun-setelah-apple-macintosh-pertama-dirilis/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[YosemiteSanFranciscoFont ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://github.com/wellsriley/YosemiteSanFranciscoFont"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-24T22:52:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/san-fransisco-yosemite-font</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>OS X Yosemite hadir dengan Helvetica Neue sebagai system font namun sayangnya, pada Mac dengan non-retina display font ini akan sedikit susah dibaca dan terkesan <em>blurry</em>. San Fransisco font, yang akan digunakan untuk Apple Watch ini mungkin bisa jadi solusi penganti Helvetica Neue di OS X Yosemite.</p>

<p><img src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/sanfransiscofonts1.png" title="YosemiteSanFransiscoFont1" ></p>

<p><img src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/sanfransiscofonts2.png" title="YosemiteSanFransiscoFont2" ></p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/san-fransisco-yosemite-font/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Maestro Macro: Quoting a Website in Markdown — The Brooks Review ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://brooksreview.net/2013/07/keyboard-maestro-macro-quoting-a-website-in-markdown/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-24T22:27:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/keyboard-maestro-quoting-a-website-in-markdown</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>The benefit is that now I can select text on a page, hit the hot key and paste to my document, saving a bunch of extra clicks. It’s not the best, but it sped things up a touch for me.</p></blockquote>

<p>Waini! Makin mudah lagi bikin postingan <em>linked list</em>. Tapi kalau pas kerja di Windows tetep aja kudu copy-paste manual.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/keyboard-maestro-quoting-a-website-in-markdown/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Bekerja Multi-Platform Mac-Windows]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/bekerja-multi-platform-mac-windows/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-24T19:37:21+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/bekerja-multi-platform-mac-windows</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bekerja menggunakan dua sistem operasi yang berbeda pastilah menjadi pengalaman yang kurang menyenangkan. Aplikasi yang digunakan juga tak jarang hanya tersedia untuk satu platform sistem operasi tertentu. Sebagai seseorang yang bekerja di dua platform, Windows di kantor dan Mac ketika di rumah, setidaknya saya harus memastikan bahwa bekerja di kedua platform sistem operasi ini sedikit lebih menyenangkan dari biasanya. Ya, paling tidak untuk sementara waktu.</p>

<!--more-->


<h3>Windows Management</h3>

<ul>
<li>Mac: <a href="http://www.bettertouchtool.net/">BetterTouchTool</a></li>
<li>Windows: <a href="http://www.winsplit-revolution.com/">WinSplit</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Melakukan <em>resize</em> jendela aplikasi meski sebentar pastilah tetap membutuhkan waktu, coba sesekali hitung akumulasi waktu tersebut dalam sehari? Bukan jumlah yang sedikit pastinya. <a href="https://twitter.com/sayzlim">Sayzlim</a> lewat tulisan di <a href="http://sayzlim.net/bettertouchtool-windows-management/">blognya</a> memaparkan dengan jelas bagaimana cara mengorganisir jendela aplikasi menggunakan BetterTouchTool dan cara ini saya pakai sampai sekarang ketika bekerja di Mac.</p>

<p>Lain halnya di Windows, meski memiliki fitur Aero Snap untuk pengaturan ukuran jendela aplikasi namun untuk dapat menggunakannya pengguna harus melakukan <em>drag</em> jendela aplikasi ke pinggir layar dan menurut saya solusi ini kurang praktis dibandingkan dengan <em>keyboard shortcuts</em>. Setelah <em>googling</em> akhirnya saya menemukan sebuah aplikasi bernaman WinSplit Revolution yang sayangnya sudah discontinue, namun tenang karena SourceForge memiliki <em>mirror download link</em> (google always know where&rsquo;s the download link, anyway). Penggunaan WinSplit Revolution pun cukup praktis, cukup tekan CTRL+ALT dan angka di NumPad maka ukuran jendela aplikasi akan secara otomatis mengikuti ukuran pengaturan dari aplikasi WinSplit.</p>

<h3>Autotext</h3>

<ul>
<li>Mac: <a href="http://smilesoftware.com/TextExpander/index.html">TextExpander</a></li>
<li>Windows: <a href="http://www.phraseexpress.com/">PhraseExpress</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Mungkin sebagian masih ada yang berpikir mengapa masih menggunakan autotext untuk melakukan sebuah pekerjaan. Selain bekerja di kantor, saya juga menulis lepas untuk sebuah blog. Menulis menggunakan <a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/">markdown</a> (one of the greatest thing that enhances writing experiences, try it!) akan jauh lebih menyenangkan menggunakan snippets yang berisi <em>markdown formatting syntax</em>. Dengan demikian yang perlu benar-benar dipikirkan adalah bagaimana menyelesaikan sebuah artikel atau tulisan yang sedang dikerjakan.</p>

<p>Tak hanya snippets yang berisi <em>markdown formatting syntax</em> PhraseExpress ataupun TextExpander juga dapat membantu saya berpindah antar direktori dengan cepat. Terlebih Explorer di Windows memang tak menyenangkan bagi yang sering bekerja dengan banyak folder. Bikin saja snippets yang akan ter-<em>expand</em> menjadi alamat direktori yang sering dikunjungi dan tekan enter. Boom! Tiba deh di direktori atau folder yang diinginkan. Keduanya baik PhraseExpress ataupun TextExpander dapat mengakomodasi kebutuhan saya akan sebuah aplikasi autotext.</p>

<h3>Text Editor</h3>

<ul>
<li>Mac: <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/byword/id420212497?mt=12">Byword</a> dan <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/ia-writer/id439623248?mt=12&amp;uo=4&amp;at=10l4LV&amp;ct=w">iA Writer</a></li>
<li>Windows: <a href="https://www.sublimetext.com/">Sublime Text 3</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Menulis memang bukan hal baru lagi bagi saya namun baru akhir-akhir ini saya bekerja paruh waktu menulis untuk sebuah blog teknologi. Platform Mac sendiri tak pernah kehabisan atau sepi dari berbagai <em>text editor</em> yang berkualitas. Favorit saya ada dua Byword dan iA Writer. Byword karena terintegrasi dengan platform publishi seperti Wordpress, Tumblr dan Blogspot juga iA Writer yang memiliki <em>typhography</em> yang apik dalam aplikasinya menjadikan pengalaman menulis jauh lebih menyenangkan.</p>

<p>Windows? Jangan tanya. Meski banyak text editor yang mendukung markdown syntax namun tak ada yang benar-benar bagus ataupun setidaknya menyamai aplikasi yang ada pada platform Mac. Akhirnya saya melakukan kostumisasi sendiri menggunakan Sublime Text 3 dan Markdown Editing Package dari <a href="http://brettterpstra.com/2012/06/30/sublime-markdownediting-now-with-100-more-blue-cursor/">Brett Terpstra</a>. Cukup memuaskan meski masih jauh dari yang saya harapkan.</p>

<p>Masih banyak kekurangan ataupun hal yang kurang menyenangkan lainnya yang belum saya dapat atasi dari bekerja dengan menggunakan dua sistem operasi yang berbeda. Namun setidaknya saya masih bisa mentolerirnya untuk sementara waktu.</p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Merilis OS X 10.10.2 Versi Beta Untuk Para Pengembang]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-rilis-osx-10.0.2-beta-pengembang/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-24T18:36:34+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-rilis-osx-10.0.2-beta-pengembang</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/yosemite10102beta.jpg" title="OS X 10.10.2 Beta" >
3 hari setelah <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2014/11/17/apple-10-10-1-release/">merilis pembaharuan OS X 10.10.1</a> kepada publik, Apple langsung merilis OS X 10.10.2 beta kepada para pengembang untuk diuji coba.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>OS X Yosemite versi 10.10.1 yang dirilis bertujuan untuk memperbaiki bug yang terdapat pada wifi di OS X Yosemite dimana beberapa pengguna sering mengalami koneksi wifi yang terputus secara tiba-tiba meski nyatanya beberapa pengguna masih melaporkan bug yang sama setelah melakukan update ke OS X 10.10.1. Seperti update sebelumnya <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2014/11/20/os-x-yosemite-10-10-2-beta/">OS X 10.10.2</a> nampaknya akan hadir sebagai pembaharuan versi minor yang akan lebih banyak bertujuan untuk meningkatkan performa serta stabilitas untuk OS X Yosemite sendiri. Dengan nomor <em>build</em> 14C68k, OS X Yosemite 10.10.2 juga menghadirkan Safari versi 8.0.2 dan aplikasi Mail versi 8.2.</p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Bantu (RED) Dalam Kampanye Hari AIDS Dunia ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://www.apple.com/pr/library/2014/11/24Apple-Announces-World-AIDS-Day-2014-Campaign-for-RED-.html"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-24T11:12:51+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-red-campaign</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/applered.PNG"></p>

<blockquote><p>CUPERTINO, California—November 23, 2014— To mark World AIDS Day 2014, Apple® and leading app developers are inviting customers to help (RED) achieve the goal of an AIDS-free generation. For the next two weeks, a special section of the App Store℠ called Apps for (RED) will offer 25 apps with exclusive new content where all proceeds will go directly to the Global Fund to fight AIDS. In addition, Apple will donate a portion of sales at Apple’s retail and online stores around the world on two of the biggest shopping days of the year: Friday, November 28 and Monday, December 1.</p>

<p>“Apple is a proud supporter of (RED) because we believe the gift of life is the most important gift anyone can give,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “For eight years, our customers have been helping fight AIDS in Africa by funding life-saving treatments which are having a profoundly positive impact. This year we are launching our biggest fundraising push yet with the participation of Apple’s retail and online stores, and some of the brightest minds in the App Store are lending their talents to the effort as well.”</p></blockquote>

<p>Dalam memperingati hari AIDS dunia, Apple bekerja sama dengan <a href="http://www.red.org/en/">(RED)</a> menggelar kampanye yang bertujuan untuk mencapai generasi bebas AIDS. Dalam <a href="https://www.apple.com/red/">kampanyenya</a>, Apple akan mendonasikan penjualan yang didapat dari aplikasi atau melalui toko retailnya ke Global Funds untuk melawan AIDS. Beberapa aplikasi yang ikut mendukung kampanye ini adalah:</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/angry-birds-hd/id364234221?mt=8&amp;ign-mpt=uo%3D4">Angry Birds HD</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/clear-tasks-reminders-to-do/id493136154?mt=8&amp;ign-mpt=uo%3D4">Clear</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/monument-valley/id728293409?mt=8&amp;ign-mpt=uo%3D4">Monument Valley</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/paper-by-fiftythree/id506003812?mt=8&amp;uo=4&amp;at=10l6nh&amp;ct=ms_inline">Paper</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/fifa-15-ultimate-team-by-ea/id870794720?mt=8&amp;uo=4&amp;at=10l6nh&amp;ct=ms_inline">Fifa 15 Ultimate Team</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/clash-of-clans/id529479190?mt=8&amp;uo=4&amp;at=10l6nh&amp;ct=ms_inline">Clash Of Clans</a></li>
<li><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/rayman-fiesta-run/id657811530?mt=8&amp;uo=4&amp;at=10l6nh&amp;ct=ms_inline">Rayman Fiesta Run</a></li>
</ul>


<p>serta masih banyak lagi aplikasi yang turut serta. Kampanye ini kan berlangsung selama dua minggu mulai tanggal 24 November hingga 7 Desember 2014.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-red-campaign/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[A Note to Re/code Readers ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://recode.net/2014/11/20/a-note-to-recode-readers/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-11-22T14:56:15+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-note-to-recode-readers</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Walt Mossberg and Kara Swisher:</p>

<blockquote><p>We thought about this decision long and hard, since we do value reader opinion. But we concluded that, as social media has continued its robust growth, the bulk of discussion of our stories is increasingly taking place there, making onsite comments less and less used and less and less useful.</p></blockquote>

<p>Ya, Recode mulai menghilangkan kolom komentar untuk para pembacanya dan saya rasa ada benarnya juga. Dengan pesatnya pertumbuhan media sosial yang ada, bukan tak mungkin nantinya kolom komentar akan berganti mentions ke akun Twitter si penulis.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-note-to-recode-readers/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  </feed>