<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-16T11:46:45+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Small screen productivity ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://mattgemmell.com/small-screen-productivity/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T11:38:33+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/small-screen-produtivity</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/mattgemmell">Matt Gemmell</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>There’s something comforting about large screens; I’m well aware of that, and I feel it too. The expanse of screen-space hints at creative possibilities. You probably wouldn’t want to do full-time graphics work or app development without a large and/or additional screen, either. You can, but those are specialised disciplines where you can make a strong argument for two-up or even larger displays.
<br />
<br /> For the vast bulk of stuff that most people will want to do on a computer, though, most of the time you don’t need a desktop monster. I don’t think you even need a 15” screen, which is essentially a portable desktop. You just have to use a small screen productively.</p></blockquote>

<p>Dear Macbook Air user, you should read this.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/small-screen-produtivity/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Monument Valley in Numbers ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://blog.monumentvalleygame.com/blog/2015/1/15/monument-valley-in-numbers"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T10:34:18+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Take a look at the statistic and how the revenue from iOS almost dominate all the revenue they get. Also remember that only 40% iOS user <a href="https://twitter.com/ustwogames/status/552136427904184320">paid for the game</a>.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Things for iPhone and iPad updated with new Notification Center widget ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2015/01/15/things-todo-nc-widget/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-16T07:57:08+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Via <a href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/">iDownloadblog</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Popular task managing app Things pushed out an update to its iPhone and iPad clients today, bringing both apps to version 2.6. The symmetrical updates bring improvements to the URI scheme, for better inter-app communication, and a new Notification Center Widget.</p></blockquote>

<p>Update! Update! I love Things than the other popular task management apps. Its simplicity and easy to use is one of main reason I choose Things. This update makes easier to glance at what you’ve to do through Notification Center. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Redesigned and Reimagined Macintosh ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://curved.de/news/curvedlabs-ein-facelift-fuer-den-macintosh-198570"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-14T09:39:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/redesigned-and-reimagined-macintosh</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/images/macintosh.jpg" /></p>

<p>What if the original Macintosh is getting redesigned? Maybe this rendering is the answer but from its thinness it looks like a docked iPad, IMHO. Anyway, I love the space gray color.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/redesigned-and-reimagined-macintosh/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[A Teenager’s View on Social Media ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://medium.com/backchannel/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media-1df945c09ac6"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-12T08:46:27+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Those are some reasons why many people my age tend to use Instagram more than they do Facebook. Everything about the application makes it less commercialized and more focused on the content, meaning more teens are inclined to visit it. When we do visit the application it is a much more pleasant experience so we are more inclined to Like and interact with the posts more. This increases our interaction with the application, meaning we will use it more, etc.</p></blockquote>

<p>A very nice read about how social media nowadays change how people are reached by each others, but still as my parents said, making call is still the easiest one.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-teenagers-view-on-social-media/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[TAG Heuer And The Future Of The Luxury Watch ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://mattrichman.net/post/107317484498/tag-heuer-and-the-future-of-the-luxury-watch"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-09T17:34:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Matt Richman:</p>
<blockquote><p>In order to have even a chance of being as feature-rich as Apple Watch, then, TAG’s smartwatch will have to pair with an Android phone. However, TAG wearers aren’t Android users. Rich people buy TAG watches, but rich people don’t buy Android phones.</p><p>This is TAG’s dilemma. Its smartwatch will need to pair with an Android phone to be anywhere near as feature-rich as Apple Watch, but TAG wearers don’t buy Android phones.</p></blockquote>

<p>Couldn’t agree more, dan sudah sepantasnya memang Matt menutup artikelnya dengan: “This, I believe, is why Jony Ive said, “Switzerland is fucked”.”</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Perspective ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-06T11:32:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/">Joe Cieplinski</a> write responses about Marco’s thought:</p>
<blockquote><p>Almost two years ago, I suggested that Apple would be better off slowing down and taking a year off to fix bugs and enhance already existing features, rather than continue the fevered pace of innovation that it had maintained for so many years. Clearly, Tim Cook ignored my advice. And how could he not? After Jobs’ death, the world consistently questioned Cook’s ability to keep the company in its role as the richest, most powerful, and innovative tech company in the universe. He had a lot to prove. There were expectations that needed to be met, and so he met them.
<br />
<br />Unfortunately, meeting those expectations has had consequences.
<br />
<br />You can’t have it both ways. You can’t stay way ahead of the curve and not introduce some bugs along the way. This decline in software quality is a side-effect of the current strategy. It’s a compromise Apple has made in order to reassure the general public that the company isn’t “doomed” without Steve Jobs.</p></blockquote>

<p>And he put this before closing paragraph:</p>

<blockquote><p>The unfortunate reality is that “Here’s a new version that’s the same as the old version, except now everything works” is a tough sell.</p></blockquote>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/balance/">Macstories</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>What it comes down to, really, is balance. I believe that Apple used to be more disciplined at balancing its desire for new features and commitment to refinements.</p></blockquote>

<p>Sure, Apple has a lot of things in their to do list. As I wrote <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/that-goddamn-truth/">last night</a>, many new features will also bring a new bugs and maybe impact on stability. Does current Apple’s software quality decline? Yes it does. Does it just work like ever before? Yes but I’m not sure I’ll answer it wholeheartedly. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[That Goddamn Truth ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.marco.org/2015/01/04/apple-lost-functional-high-ground"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-05T22:12:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>I suspect the rapid decline of Apple’s software is a sign that marketing is too high a priority at Apple today: having major new releases every year is clearly impossible for the engineering teams to keep up with while maintaining quality. Maybe it’s an engineering problem, but I suspect not — I doubt that any cohesive engineering team could keep up with these demands and maintain significantly higher quality.</p><p><br />The problem seems to be quite simple: they’re doing too much, with unrealistic deadlines.</p><p><br />We don’t need major OS releases every year. We don’t need each OS release to have a huge list of new features. We need our computers, phones, and tablets to work well first so we can enjoy new features released at a healthy, gradual, sustainable pace.</p></blockquote>

<p>That goddamn truth! I don’t deny that iOS and OS X are rapidly growing over these 2 years. Many features and improvements they put at their software but it also increase the bugs, crashes and inconsistency. So many things are broken and need to be fixed. At least they need to slow down the software upgrade cycle and start to fix everything they broke.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazing Resources for Designers: Colour ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://theultralinx.com/2015/01/amazing-resources-designers-colour.html"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-05T11:43:45+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/amazing-resources-color-theultralinx</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Therefore, we’re presenting you with a collection of awesome resources that will help you convert colour values, generate swatches, and give a hint about what hues would go well with the one you client fell in love with.</p></blockquote>

<p>GOLD! </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/amazing-resources-color-theultralinx/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Quitting Family Sharing — MacSparky ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://macsparky.com/blog/2015/1/quitting-family-sharing"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-02T21:13:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/family-sharing-problem</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="!g" title="twitter macsparky">David Spark</a> menulis tentang Family Sharing:</p>
<blockquote><p>Family Sharing is a great idea. Families, like mine, have growing children that will one day leave the nest and need iTunes accounts of their own. Moreover, Apple now has multiple device categories resulting in families hitting their head against the 10-device limit as the kids start growing up and iPhones, iPads, and Macs multiply. For a few years now, we’ve had to decide which of our devices get iTunes Match and which don’t. It’s quite frustrating that we can’t share music we’ve paid for across all our devices.</p></blockquote>

<p>Bagi sebuah keluarga yang menggunakan perangkat iOS dan Mac menggunakan Family Sharing memang lebih menguntungkan, pasalnya mereka dapat saling berbagi aplikasi, lagu, ataupun film yang cukup dibeli dari satu akun saja. Namun ternyata menggunakan Family Sharing tak semenyenagkan yang dibayangkan. </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/family-sharing-problem/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe life into an old Mac — 512 Pixels ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.512pixels.net/blog/2014/12/breathe-live-into-an-old-mac"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-01T22:49:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/breathe-life-into-old-mac</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Joe Caiati menulis di <a href="http://www.512pixels.net">512 Pixels</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Luckily, older Macs are more flexible with hardware upgrades and coupled with third-party software, you can unlock features that Apple doesn’t support on older models. Here is how to get the most life out of an aging Mac.</p></blockquote>

<p>Perangkat Mac memang tak terbilang murah, untuk itulah pengguna harus pintar-pintar mencari cara bagaimana agar Mac yang telah lama dimiliki tetap memiliki performa yang baik. Biasanya, Mac versi lama memiliki beberapa komponen yang dapat diupgrade sendiri oleh pemiliknya dan mengganti RAM atau hard drive dengan spesifikasi yang lebih baik bisa menjadi alternatif untuk mengembalikan performa Mac yang dirasa sudah mulai menurun.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/breathe-life-into-old-mac/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year, guys!]]></title>
  	<link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/happy-new-year/"/>
  	
    <updated>2015-01-01T22:19:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/happy-new-year</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>Happy New Year, guys!</em></p>

<p>Tahun 2014 sudah berlalu dan tentu saja banyak pengalaman serta pembelajaran yang saya dapat. 2014 merupakan tahun yang luar biasa, penuh kesempatan, kejutan serta hal-hal tak terduga sebelumnya. </p>

<p>Mendapat kesempatan untuk bekerja <em>part-time</em> di sebuah blog teknologi ternama di tanah air, belajar membuat blog tentang teknologi menggunakan platform <a href="!g" title="octopress">Octopress</a>, mengetahui serta belajar tentang <em>iOS automation</em> dari berbagai blog dan masih banyak lagi</p>

<p>Jika ditanya tentang harapan di 2015 maka jawabannya adalah konsistensi. Ya, saya ingin punya konsistensi untuk mengerjakan hal yang telah saya mulai seperti halnya rajin menulis di blog ini yang pernah membuat saya tak tertidur di malam hari. Blog yang berisi kumpulan berita serta informasi tentang teknologi.</p>

<p><em>Let’s have an awesome 2015!</em></p>
]]></content>
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[My Must-Have iPhone Apps, 2014 Edition – MacStories ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macstories.net/roundups/my-must-have-iphone-apps-2014-edition/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-30T23:47:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/must-have-iphone-apps-2014</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Frederico Viticci</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>At the end of the article, you’ll also find my iPhone App of the Year and a Runner-up. Each app has a direct iTunes link, and, where possible, I’ve included links to previous MacStories coverage as well.</p></blockquote>

<p>Saya selalu suka membaca setiap artikel <a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Frederico Viticci</a> di <a href="http://www.macstories.net">Macstories</a>. Tak hanya menyajikan review, namun <a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> juga mengulasnya secara komprehensif dan mendalam. </p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/must-have-iphone-apps-2014/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitag: batch Finder tagging from the command line ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://brettterpstra.com/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-27T20:44:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/bretttrepstra-vitag-release</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/ttscoff">Brett Trepstra</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Run without arguments it grabs all files and folders in the current directory and opens your text editor with a list of them, each one followed by its current tags (if any) in square brackets. Edit what’s in the brackets, save and close, and those changes are immediately applied.</p></blockquote>

<p>Brett memang tak pernah kehabisan akal tentang bagaimana mengembangkan workflow yang dimiliki serta menjadikannya lebih efektif dan efisien. Kali ini ia merilis sebuah program berupa perintah baris untuk mempercepat tagging files atau folder di OS X 10.9+. Selamat mencoba! </p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/bretttrepstra-vitag-release/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Holidays! All Field Guides are On Sale — MacSparky ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://macsparky.com/blog/2014/12/happy-holidays-all-field-guides-are-on-sale"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-25T22:38:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/macsparky-field-guides-sale</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/macsparky">David Sparks</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>This holiday season I&#8217;ve put all of the MacSparky Field Guides on sale.</p></blockquote>
<p>SALE! SALE! SALE! Happy holiday, guys!</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/macsparky-field-guides-sale/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Issues Network Time Protocol Security Fix for OS X Users ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.macrumors.com/2014/12/22/apple-issues-new-security-fix/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-23T09:25:40+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-issues-network-time-protocol-security-fix</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="www.macrumors.com">MacRumors</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Apple today released a new security update that’s designed to address a &#8220;critical security issue&#8221; with the Network Time Protocol service on OS X. Apple recommends that all Yosemite, Mavericks, and Mountain Lion users install the update &#8220;as soon as possible.&#8221;</p></blockquote>

<p>Update! Update!</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-issues-network-time-protocol-security-fix/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Analytics di Twitter for iPhone ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="https://support.twitter.com/articles/320043-tweet-activity-dashboard"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-23T09:09:04+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/twitter-analytics-di-twitter-for-iphone</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://support.twitter.com">Twitter Support Page</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>On mobile (currently available on Twitter for iPhone), click on one of your Tweets to get to the Tweet detail page, then tap “View Tweet activity.” Make sure you have installed the latest version of Twitter for iPhone.</p></blockquote>

<p>Sekarang, saya memiliki satu alasan kenapa harus menginstall aplikasi resmi Twitter di perangkat iOS saya.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/twitter-analytics-di-twitter-for-iphone/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Allarm: a cleverly named tweak that toggles all alarm clocks simultaneously ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2014/12/21/allarm-toggle-all-alarms/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-22T16:09:27+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/allarm-toogle-all-alarm-simultaneously</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.twitter.com/jeffbenjam/">Jeff Benjamin</a> via <a href="www.idownloadblog.com">iDownbloadblog</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Once you install Allarm, simply head over to the alarm clock tab of the Clock app, and you’ll see a brand new Toggle All Alarms toggle at the top of the page.</p></blockquote>

<p>Memiliki sebuah iPhone yang sudah terjailbreak dan suka mengatur alarm dengan selang waktu 15 menit (ehem!)? Tweak ini pastilah sangat berguna.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/allarm-toogle-all-alarm-simultaneously/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing Photo Metadata with Metapho — MacSparky ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://macsparky.com/blog/2014/12/removing-photo-metadata-with-metapho"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-22T14:57:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/removing-photo-metadata-with-metapho</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="!g" title="twitter macsparky">David Sparks</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The app is easy enough to use. Select an existing photo and push the big red button to remove the metadata.</p></blockquote>

<p>Menghilangkan metadata dari sebuah foto kini menjadi mudah berkat <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/metapho-manage-photo-metadata/id914457352?ls=1&amp;mt=8?at=10laz7&amp;ct=blog">Metapho</a>. Bagi yang menaruh perhatian lebih terkait masalah keamanan atau privasi maka in-app-purchase seharga 2$ dalam aplikasi ini bukanlah sebuah masalah besar.</p>
<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/removing-photo-metadata-with-metapho/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    
  	<title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Drafts for? - All this ∞ ]]></title><!-- add in a glyph or [link-post] here so people know where they're ending up -->
  	<link href="http://www.leancrew.com/all-this/2014/12/what-is-drafts-for/"/>
  	
    <updated>2014-12-18T22:59:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/whats-drafts-for</id>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/drdrang">Dr. Drang</a> memberikan dua alasan mengapa <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/id/app/drafts-4-quickly-capture-notes/id905337691?mt=8&amp;uo=4">Drafts 4</a> layak berada di homescreen para pengguna perangkat iOS.</p>

<a rel="full-article" href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/whats-drafts-for/">Permalink</a>]]></content><!-- add in a glyph or some way to denote that the permalink goes back to your site -->
  	
  </entry>
  
  </feed>