<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: tips | Sweet Distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/tips/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-26T17:12:25+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Tasks In Things Using Do Notes]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/create-tasks-in-things-using-do-notes.markdown/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-21T00:59:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/create-tasks-in-things-using-do-notes.markdown</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A few weeks ago I wrote about how to <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/Chaining-Things-and-iOS-Reminders-with-IFTTT/">chaining Things and web automation service IFTTT</a>. This workaround comes because I have to use PC at work and since my choice app of GTD is Things then I need to sort this problem out. Even I can pick up my iPhone and write down the task directly to <a href="https://culturedcode.com">Things</a> inbox, it’s not a pleasant things to do. 
<!--more--></p>

<p>I have <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/drafts-4-quickly-capture-notes/id905337691?mt=8&amp;at=1010lDx&amp;ct=sd">Drafts</a> installed on my iPhone and since it’s a place where text start on iOS, I mainly used it to save article for a blog post ideas. I also use Drafts for do brain dump and send to Things inbox later but what about if I want to quickly capture ideas that suddenly pop-up and I need to get out of it from my mind soon? This is where <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/do-note-by-ifttt/id905998379&amp;at=1010lDx&amp;ct=sd">Do Note</a> by IFTTT take a role.</p>

<p>With my impulsiveness, my mind is unpredictable. Sometimes an idea pop-up in the wrong place and time. To get this idea out of my mind as quickly as possible, I use Do Note. I only need a recipe that makes a task/idea in iOS reminders. Things have reminders integration so whenever I take a note using Do Note and send them to iOS reminders, Things will pick and save it to its inbox. One thing you should pay attention is you have to choose the same iOS reminder list between Do Notes and Things.</p>

<p>The only caveats using this method is sometimes the task/ idea that’s made using Do Note doesn’t appear automatically neither in iOS reminder or Things. I guess it needs to be synced first before the task/ ideas appear. </p>

<p>I know that Drafts could make multiple to-dos to Things inbox and even you can add notes but for an ideas/ tasks that need to get out soon, you can use Do Notes just like I do. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Play a Power Charging Sound Effect in OS X When a MacBook is Plugged in (Like iOS)]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/play-sound-effect-in-osx-like-iOS/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-18T08:18:05+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/play-sound-effect-in-osx-like-iOS</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Seems interesting, let’s try!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone Extensions Trick]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-iphone-extensions-trick/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-16T11:22:32+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-iphone-extensions-trick</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a trick everyone should know.
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>When creating a contact, instead of this:</p></p><p><p>Jenny<br/>866-5309 x1982</p></p><p><p>Do this:</p></p><p><p>Jenny<br/>866-5309;1982</p></p><p><p>The semicolon is secret code to your iPhone to wait once the call connects and gives you the option to dial the extension when you tap it at the bottom of the screen.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Custom Function in Google Sheets]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/google-sheets-custom-functions/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-20T09:53:39+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/google-sheets-custom-functions</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nice tips how you can write functions using JavaScript in Google Sheets.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
