<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Macstories | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/macstories/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-17T17:07:39+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life After Cancer: How the iPhone Helped Me Achieve a Healthier Lifestyle]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-04T07:46:22+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/live-after-cancer-macstories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> wrote a story that everyone should read:</p>

<p><blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Since being diagnosed with Hodgkin Lymphoma (Stage IV) in late 2011, my life changed. Beyond the psychological and emotional consequences of how cancer affected me, my family, and my relationships, it is undeniable and abundantly clear that cancer took its toll on me from a physical perspective.</p></p><p><p>Last year, I decided to regain control of my body, my life habits, and my health. I started tracking everything I could about my activities, my exercise routine, the food I ate, and the time I spent working with my iPad instead of walking, sleeping, or enjoying time with my family. Since then, I’ve made a decision to not let cancer and its consequences define me any longer.</p></p><p><p>I want to be healthier, I want to eat better, and I want to take the second chance I was given and make the most of it. What started as an experiment has become a new daily commitment to improve my lifestyle and focus.</p></p><p><p>And it wouldn’t be possible without my iPhone.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Have you ever wondered how a product of a company could change people’s life? A good company not only built a product to make money but also built a product which can change people’s life. </p>

<p>Go, send <a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> writings on your favorite read-later service.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Must-Have iPhone Apps, 2014 Edition – MacStories]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/must-have-iphone-apps-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-30T23:47:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/must-have-iphone-apps-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Frederico Viticci</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>At the end of the article, you’ll also find my iPhone App of the Year and a Runner-up. Each app has a direct iTunes link, and, where possible, I’ve included links to previous MacStories coverage as well.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Saya selalu suka membaca setiap artikel <a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Frederico Viticci</a> di <a href="http://www.macstories.net">Macstories</a>. Tak hanya menyajikan review, namun <a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">@viticci</a> juga mengulasnya secara komprehensif dan mendalam. </p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Clients in 2014: An Exploration of Tweetbot, Twitterrific, and Twitter for iOS]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/twitter-clients-2014-macstories/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-11T10:58:41+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/twitter-clients-2014-macstories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Frederico Viticci</a> via <a href="www.macstories.net">Macstories</a>:
<blockquote><p>Choosing a Twitter client is incredibly personal. This experiment reinforced my belief that most of my criticism for Tweetbot and Twitterrific stems from API limitations that Twitter won’t fix for third-party developers. For this reason, it would be wrong to judge third-party clients solely based on features they can’t implement.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Seperti biasa, Frederico Viticci melakukan pekerjaan yang mengaggumkan dengan menghadirkan ulasan yang komprehensif tentang berbagai macam <em>twitter client</em> di iOS seperti Tweetbot, Twitterific, dll. Namun meski banyak sekali pilihan aplikasi pihak ketiga untuk bermain Twitter namun bagi saya Tweetbot merupakan aplikasi yang paling pas dan menyenangkan untuk digunakan. Selamat membaca!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With JavaScript for Automation on Yosemite]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/javascript-for-automation/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-03T10:31:41+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/javascript-for-automation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/The_Axx">Alex Guyot</a> via <a href="www.macstories.net">Macstories</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Automating applications on OS X is an extremely powerful ability, and can save you huge amounts of time. My simple iTunes automation scripts are just conveniences, but the ideas behind them can be appropriated to other, more powerful apps to great effect. If you take the time to evaluate some of your common Mac workflows and take a look at the built-in methods in the productivity apps you use most, you may find that you can use JXA to greatly enhance your efficiency at certain tasks.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Jika <a href="https://developer.apple.com/library/mac/documentation/AppleScript/Conceptual/AppleScriptLangGuide/introduction/ASLR_intro.html">AppleScript</a> dan <a href="http://support.apple.com/en-us/ht2488">Automator</a> dirasa tak cukup untuk mengotomatisasi berbagi pekerjaan pada Mac maka JavaScript for Automation (JXA) boleh dicoba. <a href="https://twitter.com/The_Axx">Alex Guyot</a> melalui Macstories telah memberikan sedikit gambaran dan contoh bagaimana javascript dapat mendukung mempercepat workflow di OS X.</p>

<p>Let’s automate all the things!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[#MacStoriesDeals Black Friday 2014: Best Deals for iPhone, iPad, and Mac Apps & Games]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-27T09:14:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://macstories.net">Macstories</a>
&gt; Black Friday is upon us once again! #MacStoriesDeals is the best place to find great deals for iOS apps and games, Mac software, and more.</p>

<p>Macstories telah merangkum beberapa deals diskon aplikasi baik untuk iPhone, iPad hingga Mac menjelang Black Friday. </p>

<p>Fantastical 2 yang menjadi aplikasi kalender favorit saya juga ada dalam daftar, kini hanya $1.99 untuk iPhone dan $4.99 untuk iPad serta $9.99 untuk Mac. Jika belum yakin untuk mencoba Fantastical 2 maka sebaiknya baca dulu <a href="http://www.macstories.net/reviews/fantastical-2-review/">review</a> dari Macstories.</p>

<p>Selain deals di atas, <a href="http://smilesoftware.com/TextExpander/touch/index.html">Text Expander Touch</a> menjadi Rp. 12 Ribu di App Store Indonesia. Namun ketika saya membuka App Store US, harga dari Text Expander Touch masih sama yaitu $4.99. </p>

<p>So, stay update!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
