<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Idownloadblog | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/idownloadblog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-04T10:59:57+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things for iPhone and iPad Updated With New Notification Center Widget]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-16T07:57:08+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/things-update</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Via <a href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/">iDownloadblog</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Popular task managing app Things pushed out an update to its iPhone and iPad clients today, bringing both apps to version 2.6. The symmetrical updates bring improvements to the URI scheme, for better inter-app communication, and a new Notification Center Widget.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Update! Update! I love Things than the other popular task management apps. Its simplicity and easy to use is one of main reason I choose Things. This update makes easier to glance at what you’ve to do through Notification Center. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allarm: A Cleverly Named Tweak That Toggles All Alarm Clocks Simultaneously]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/allarm-toogle-all-alarm-simultaneously/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-22T16:09:27+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/allarm-toogle-all-alarm-simultaneously</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.twitter.com/jeffbenjam/">Jeff Benjamin</a> via <a href="www.idownloadblog.com">iDownbloadblog</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Once you install Allarm, simply head over to the alarm clock tab of the Clock app, and you’ll see a brand new Toggle All Alarms toggle at the top of the page.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Memiliki sebuah iPhone yang sudah terjailbreak dan suka mengatur alarm dengan selang waktu 15 menit (ehem!)? Tweak ini pastilah sangat berguna.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[FileBrowser: An Alternative to iFile?]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/filebrowser-ifile-alternatives/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-05T09:16:41+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/filebrowser-ifile-alternatives</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="@JeffBenjam">Jeff Benjam</a> via <a href="www.idownloadblog.com">iDownloadblog</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>FileBrowser allows jailbroken users to browse the entire filesystem of an iPad, iPhone, or iPod touch. It lends the ability to do things like rename, copy &amp; paste, create and delete folders, delete files, create and extract compressed files, and more.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Jika membaca review yang ditulis oleh Jeff, rasanya FileBrowser masih jauh baik secara fitur atau tampilan jika dibandingkan dengan iFile. Hadir secara gratis dengan adanya iklan dalam aplikasinya, FileBrowser bisa jadi alternatif untuk berjelajah antar direktori pada perangkat iOS. Namun jangan lupa bahwa iFile juga dapat digunakan secara gratis meski dengan fitur yang terbatas.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
