<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: apple | Sweet Distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/apple/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-28T09:50:41+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Apple and Samsung Industrial Design]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-difference-between-apple-and-samsung/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-28T09:30:49+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-difference-between-apple-and-samsung</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/reneritchie">Rene Ritchie</a> writes for iMore about difference between Apple and Samsung:
<blockquote><p>To align everything along the edge of a device takes designing and mounting the boards in a certain way, and the ports and speakers, and the buttons and jacks, and the grills and every other detail so they all line up at exactly the right place at the end. Painstaking is likely an understatement.</p></p><p><p>Is it worth the effort? For me, as a customer, knowing that Apple had the consideration and took the time and effort to align their hardware speaks to the overall quality of their work. It reassures me that the same consideration and effort were likely spent making sure not a millimeter nor milliamp of battery space was wasted, not a nanometer of die, not a gap left around the screen, or a dead zone in the capacitive sensor.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>And he sums everything about Samsung’s product design in one sentences: 
<blockquote><p>Almost nothing is aligned.</p></blockquote></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Cook on Apple's Future: Everything Can Change Except Values]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/fast-company-tim-cook-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-28T16:21:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/fast-company-tim-cook-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tim Cook on <a href="http://www.fastcompany.com/3042435/steves-legacy-tim-looks-ahead">FastCompany</a> interview:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>There’s this thing in technology, almost a disease, where the definition of success is making the most. How many clicks did you get, how many active users do you have, how many units did you sell? Everybody in technology seems to want big numbers. Steve never got carried away with that. He focused on making the best.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>GOLD!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Pricing of Apple Watch]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-watch-pricing/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-21T08:42:36+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-watch-pricing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting thought of<a href="https://twitter.com/gruber">John Gruber</a> about Apple Watch pricing: 
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Apple Watch Edition is not a tech product, so don’t try to price it like one.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>I love the footnote of his post: </p>

<p><blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>At prices like these, an Apple Watch Edition is not an accessory for your iPhone — your iPhone is an accessory for your Apple Watch Edition. </p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Tim Cook at the Goldman Sachs Conference]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-12T09:25:04+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/settern">Serenity Caldwell</a> made a transcipt for iMore about Tim Cook talks at the Goldman Sachs Conferences. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Apple Made Milk]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-27T09:15:44+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What if Apple and others popular brand do packaging to your daily needs at grocery?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
