<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Apple | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/apple/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-16T10:38:29+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TAG Heuer and the Future of the Luxury Watch]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-09T17:34:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Matt Richman:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>In order to have even a chance of being as feature-rich as Apple Watch, then, TAG’s smartwatch will have to pair with an Android phone. However, TAG wearers aren’t Android users. Rich people buy TAG watches, but rich people don’t buy Android phones.</p></p><p><p>This is TAG’s dilemma. Its smartwatch will need to pair with an Android phone to be anywhere near as feature-rich as Apple Watch, but TAG wearers don’t buy Android phones.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Couldn’t agree more, dan sudah sepantasnya memang Matt menutup artikelnya dengan: “This, I believe, is why Jony Ive said, “Switzerland is fucked”.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Perspective]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-06T11:32:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/">Joe Cieplinski</a> write responses about Marco’s thought:
<blockquote><p>Almost two years ago, I suggested that Apple would be better off slowing down and taking a year off to fix bugs and enhance already existing features, rather than continue the fevered pace of innovation that it had maintained for so many years. Clearly, Tim Cook ignored my advice. And how could he not? After Jobs’ death, the world consistently questioned Cook’s ability to keep the company in its role as the richest, most powerful, and innovative tech company in the universe. He had a lot to prove. There were expectations that needed to be met, and so he met them.</p></p><p><p>Unfortunately, meeting those expectations has had consequences.</p></p><p><p>You can’t have it both ways. You can’t stay way ahead of the curve and not introduce some bugs along the way. This decline in software quality is a side-effect of the current strategy. It’s a compromise Apple has made in order to reassure the general public that the company isn’t “doomed” without Steve Jobs.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>And he put this before closing paragraph:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>The unfortunate reality is that “Here’s a new version that’s the same as the old version, except now everything works” is a tough sell.</p></blockquote></p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/balance/">Macstories</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>What it comes down to, really, is balance. I believe that Apple used to be more disciplined at balancing its desire for new features and commitment to refinements.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Sure, Apple has a lot of things in their to do list. As I wrote <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/that-goddamn-truth/">last night</a>, many new features will also bring a new bugs and maybe impact on stability. Does current Apple’s software quality decline? Yes it does. Does it just work like ever before? Yes but I’m not sure I’ll answer it wholeheartedly. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps Cannot Use Push Notifications to Send Promotions, Unless You’re Apple or Anyone Else]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-02T10:20:38+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>If Apple won’t enforce its own standards against spamming and annoying customers — which really isn’t good enough — the least they can do is practice the rules themselves and be a good example.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Maybe Apple just being consistent to what its CEO said back to WWDC this year: “This is something only Apple could do.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple vs Jailbreak]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-01T23:03:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.apple.com/legal/sales-support/sales-policies/retail_us.html">Apple</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>Making unauthorized modifications to the software on an iPhone violates the iPhone software license agreement. The common term for modifying an iPhone is jail-breaking, with a particular emphasis on the second part of that term. That’s why we strongly, almost emphatically, recommend that you do not do so. Really. Should you be unable to use your iPhone due to an unauthorized software modification, its repair will not be covered under the warranty.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Apple memang sudah lama menentang ataupun tak mengijinkan penggunanya untuk melakukan jailbreak. Pada halaman <em>sales policy</em> di atas bahkan Apple tak bertanggung jawab atas kerusakan yang terjadi akibat modifikasi dari sistem operasi iOS dalam hal ini berarti hangusnya garansi perangkat.</p>

<!--more-->

<p>Keputusan untuk melakukan jailbreak memang sepenuhnya ada di tangan pengguna dan tak selamanya jailbreak berdampak buruk. Bagi seorang pengembang ataupun seseorang yang ingin mempelajari tentang sistem operasi terutama iOS, jailbreak bisa saja merupakan sebuah langkah untuk mendukung kegiatannya. Tak hanya itu, jailbreak yang membuka akses <em>root</em> perangkat juga memungkinkan pengguna untuk mengkustomisasi perangkat yang dimiliki mulai dari menginstall tema, mengubah ikon batere atau sinyal, menghilangkan UI yang dianggap mengganggu dan masih banyak lagi. Namun juga tak jarang beberapa orang melakukan jailbreak untuk mengunduh dan menginstall aplikasi bajakan yang tentu saja merugikan bagi pengembang aplikasi padahal banyak cara untuk mendapatkan sebuah aplikasi secara legal, memakai iTunes gift card misalnya.</p>

<p>Memang secara teori, jailbreak bisa dihilangkan cukup dengan melakukan restore perangkat menggunakan iTunes apabila ingin melakukan klaim garansi, namun jika terjadi hal yang tak diinginkan semisal <em>brick</em> pada perangkat karena tak sengaja melakukan <em>Reset All Settings</em> maka siapa yang akan bertanggung jawab? Oleh sebab itu mengapa jailbreak selalu disertai dengan <em>disclaimer</em>: DWYOR (Do With Your Own Risk)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Apple Keeps AirDrop Files Private and Secure | iMore]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/how-apple-keeps-airdrop-files/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-29T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/how-apple-keeps-airdrop-files</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/reneritchie">Rene Ritchie</a> di iMore:
&gt; ## Encrypted identities</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>When AirDrop is turned on, a 2048-bit RSA Identity is created and stored on your iPhone, iPad, or Mac. A hash, based on the phone numbers and/or email addresses associated with your Apple ID, is also created. That’ll be used later to identify you in a way that maintains your privacy and security.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Security! Security! </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
