<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Apple | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/apple/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-13T23:06:04+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Tim Cook at the Goldman Sachs Conference]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-12T09:25:04+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tim-cook-interview</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://twitter.com/settern">Serenity Caldwell</a> made a transcipt for iMore about Tim Cook talks at the Goldman Sachs Conferences. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Apple Made Milk]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-27T09:15:44+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-made-milk</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What if Apple and others popular brand do packaging to your daily needs at grocery?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TAG Heuer and the Future of the Luxury Watch]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-09T17:34:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/tag-heuer-and-future-luxury-watches</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Matt Richman:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>In order to have even a chance of being as feature-rich as Apple Watch, then, TAG’s smartwatch will have to pair with an Android phone. However, TAG wearers aren’t Android users. Rich people buy TAG watches, but rich people don’t buy Android phones.</p></p><p><p>This is TAG’s dilemma. Its smartwatch will need to pair with an Android phone to be anywhere near as feature-rich as Apple Watch, but TAG wearers don’t buy Android phones.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Couldn’t agree more, dan sudah sepantasnya memang Matt menutup artikelnya dengan: “This, I believe, is why Jony Ive said, “Switzerland is fucked”.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Perspective]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-06T11:32:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/">Joe Cieplinski</a> write responses about Marco’s thought:
<blockquote><p>Almost two years ago, I suggested that Apple would be better off slowing down and taking a year off to fix bugs and enhance already existing features, rather than continue the fevered pace of innovation that it had maintained for so many years. Clearly, Tim Cook ignored my advice. And how could he not? After Jobs’ death, the world consistently questioned Cook’s ability to keep the company in its role as the richest, most powerful, and innovative tech company in the universe. He had a lot to prove. There were expectations that needed to be met, and so he met them.</p></p><p><p>Unfortunately, meeting those expectations has had consequences.</p></p><p><p>You can’t have it both ways. You can’t stay way ahead of the curve and not introduce some bugs along the way. This decline in software quality is a side-effect of the current strategy. It’s a compromise Apple has made in order to reassure the general public that the company isn’t “doomed” without Steve Jobs.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>And he put this before closing paragraph:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>The unfortunate reality is that “Here’s a new version that’s the same as the old version, except now everything works” is a tough sell.</p></blockquote></p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/balance/">Macstories</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>What it comes down to, really, is balance. I believe that Apple used to be more disciplined at balancing its desire for new features and commitment to refinements.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Sure, Apple has a lot of things in their to do list. As I wrote <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/that-goddamn-truth/">last night</a>, many new features will also bring a new bugs and maybe impact on stability. Does current Apple’s software quality decline? Yes it does. Does it just work like ever before? Yes but I’m not sure I’ll answer it wholeheartedly. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps Cannot Use Push Notifications to Send Promotions, Unless You’re Apple or Anyone Else]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-02T10:20:38+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>If Apple won’t enforce its own standards against spamming and annoying customers — which really isn’t good enough — the least they can do is practice the rules themselves and be a good example.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Maybe Apple just being consistent to what its CEO said back to WWDC this year: “This is something only Apple could do.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
