<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Thoughts | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/thoughts/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-17T16:59:10+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 8 Changed How I Work on My iPhone and iPad]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iOS8-stories/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-17T07:42:30+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/iOS8-stories</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> thought about iOS 8 and bunch of its features last year on Macstories:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>What I realized in using extensions is how necessary last year’s redesign of iOS was. Imagine if Apple didn’t ship a new design with iOS 7: today, we’d have sheets of stitched leather or shiny metal on top of apps that look like agendas or little robots. The cohesiveness and subdued style that iOS 7 brought with its precise structure and hierarchy allows extensions to integrate nicely with apps, feeling like extra actions rather than eerily realistic objects.</p></p><p><p>The impact of action and share extensions on my workflow has been massive even with only a few apps and bugs left in iOS 8. I use my iPad more because I spend less time switching between apps, copying text around, or moving files between different containers. I’m more efficient thanks to extensions because the quality of the software I use every day has increased considerably. I can’t imagine what we’ll start seeing today with action and share extensions on the App Store.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>When iOS 7 came out, I didn’t satisfy with the new UI. I wished there’s a way to downgrade back to iOS 6. The main reason was the unbearable lagging and blindly white all over iOS for that time. Then iOS 8 came out last year, I upgraded. Now when I look at iOS today, I would think many times to downgrade even when there’s a way to do. </p>

<p>Extensions, change how we used iOS. I could easily post to Tumblr, Path, Twitter. I could easily find a inspiring quote, make selection and save it on my Notes folder in Dropbox that also available on my nvAlt. 3rd party keyboard, let us manage multiple clipboard like <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/en/app/clips-copy-paste-anywhere/id917638056?mt=8">Clips</a> does. Finding the right emoji, now become easier, there’s <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/emoji++-fast-emoji-keyboard/id919234935?mt=8">Emoji++</a>.</p>

<p>And if I look back to iOS 6 (yeah, my friends still use iOS 6.1.3 in her iPhone 4s), it look dull and outdated.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Note to Re/code Readers]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-note-to-recode-readers/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-22T14:56:15+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/a-note-to-recode-readers</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Walt Mossberg and Kara Swisher:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We thought about this decision long and hard, since we do value reader opinion. But we concluded that, as social media has continued its robust growth, the bulk of discussion of our stories is increasingly taking place there, making onsite comments less and less used and less and less useful.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Ya, Recode mulai menghilangkan kolom komentar untuk para pembacanya dan saya rasa ada benarnya juga. Dengan pesatnya pertumbuhan media sosial yang ada, bukan tak mungkin nantinya kolom komentar akan berganti mentions ke akun Twitter si penulis. </p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
