<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Appstore | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/appstore/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-17T17:11:52+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apps Cannot Use Push Notifications to Send Promotions, Unless You’re Apple or Anyone Else]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-02T10:20:38+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/app-store-rules</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:
<blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>If Apple won’t enforce its own standards against spamming and annoying customers — which really isn’t good enough — the least they can do is practice the rules themselves and be a good example.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Maybe Apple just being consistent to what its CEO said back to WWDC this year: “This is something only Apple could do.”</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NEW 1WRITER WITH JAVASCRIPT ACTIONS]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-new-1writer-javascript-actions/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-01T14:44:17+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/the-new-1writer-javascript-actions</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/pgruneich">Philip Gruneich</a> di <a href="http://onetapless.com">OneTapLess</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>1Writer 2.0 was the most delightful surprise this week and probably the best deal you could make this holiday if you write in your iOS devices. I’m sure it is only a matter of time until more actions pop up and improve the pool of options in this outstanding text editor.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p><a href="http://1writerapp.com/">1Writer</a>, salah satu teks editor di iOS baru saja menerima pembaharuan besar. Penambahan <em>javascript action</em>, pengamanan tambahan dengan Touch ID, kustomisasi font serta tampilan, safari extensions, in-app-browser serta <em>today widget</em> untuk mengakses dokumen favorit secara cepat dan masih banyak lagi.</p>

<p>Ngoc Luu juga menambahkan <em><a href="http://1writerapp.com/actiondir">action directory</a></em> bagi pengguna yang ingin menambahkan <em>javascript action</em> dengan mudah ke dalam aplikasi 1Writer. Tak hanya itu, bagi pengguna yang ingin belajar membuat <em>javascript action</em> sendiri, Ngoc Luu juga sudah menyiapkan <a href="http://1writerapp.com/docs/js">dokumen</a> pendukung yang dapat dipelajari dan digunakan. </p>

<p>Seperti biasa, Philip Gruneich juga telah membuat artikel mengenai update dari 1Writer di OneTapLess dengan contoh <em>javascript action-nya</em>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[This App Lets You Unlock Your Mac With Touch ID]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unlock-macbook-with-touch-id/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-01T13:13:47+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/unlock-macbook-with-touch-id</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Via <a href="www.cultofmac.com">CultofMac</a></p>

<p><blockquote><p></p></p><p><p>Called FingerKey, this new utility works by using Bluetooth 4.0 (what else?) to pair with your Mac, then forms a low latency, low energy wireless connection with an extra layer of 256-bit AES encryption on top to keep things secure.</p></p><p><p>Once you’ve got things paired, unlocking your Mac is as simple as getting into Bluetooth range, opening up the app, and putting your finger against the home button. There’s also a Notification Center Widget that makes things even easier, and FingerKey can actually unlock multiple Macs at a time.</p></p><p><p></p></blockquote></p>

<p>Macbook dengan Touch ID bisa saja menjadi inovasi Apple selanjutnya, namun sebelum itu terjadi kini membuka Mac dengan Touch ID yang terdapat di iPhone sudah bisa dilakukan.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[#MacStoriesDeals Black Friday 2014: Best Deals for iPhone, iPad, and Mac Apps & Games]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-27T09:14:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/blackfriday-apps-deal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://macstories.net">Macstories</a>
&gt; Black Friday is upon us once again! #MacStoriesDeals is the best place to find great deals for iOS apps and games, Mac software, and more.</p>

<p>Macstories telah merangkum beberapa deals diskon aplikasi baik untuk iPhone, iPad hingga Mac menjelang Black Friday. </p>

<p>Fantastical 2 yang menjadi aplikasi kalender favorit saya juga ada dalam daftar, kini hanya $1.99 untuk iPhone dan $4.99 untuk iPad serta $9.99 untuk Mac. Jika belum yakin untuk mencoba Fantastical 2 maka sebaiknya baca dulu <a href="http://www.macstories.net/reviews/fantastical-2-review/">review</a> dari Macstories.</p>

<p>Selain deals di atas, <a href="http://smilesoftware.com/TextExpander/touch/index.html">Text Expander Touch</a> menjadi Rp. 12 Ribu di App Store Indonesia. Namun ketika saya membuka App Store US, harga dari Text Expander Touch masih sama yaitu $4.99. </p>

<p>So, stay update!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
