<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Ios | sweet distractions]]></title>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/categories/ios/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-03T08:53:48+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aditya Daniel]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monument Valley in Numbers]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-16T10:34:18+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/monument-valley-stats</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Take a look at the statistic and how the revenue from iOS almost dominate all the revenue they get. Also remember that only 40% iOS user <a href="https://twitter.com/ustwogames/status/552136427904184320">paid for the game</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Perspective]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-06T11:32:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/another-perspective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.joecieplinski.com/blog/2015/01/05/compromises-have-consequences/">Joe Cieplinski</a> write responses about Marco’s thought:
<blockquote><p>Almost two years ago, I suggested that Apple would be better off slowing down and taking a year off to fix bugs and enhance already existing features, rather than continue the fevered pace of innovation that it had maintained for so many years. Clearly, Tim Cook ignored my advice. And how could he not? After Jobs’ death, the world consistently questioned Cook’s ability to keep the company in its role as the richest, most powerful, and innovative tech company in the universe. He had a lot to prove. There were expectations that needed to be met, and so he met them.</p></p><p><p>Unfortunately, meeting those expectations has had consequences.</p></p><p><p>You can’t have it both ways. You can’t stay way ahead of the curve and not introduce some bugs along the way. This decline in software quality is a side-effect of the current strategy. It’s a compromise Apple has made in order to reassure the general public that the company isn’t “doomed” without Steve Jobs.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>And he put this before closing paragraph:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>The unfortunate reality is that “Here’s a new version that’s the same as the old version, except now everything works” is a tough sell.</p></blockquote></p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/viticci">Federico Viticci</a> on <a href="http://www.macstories.net/stories/balance/">Macstories</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>What it comes down to, really, is balance. I believe that Apple used to be more disciplined at balancing its desire for new features and commitment to refinements.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Sure, Apple has a lot of things in their to do list. As I wrote <a href="http://sweetdistractions.net/that-goddamn-truth/">last night</a>, many new features will also bring a new bugs and maybe impact on stability. Does current Apple’s software quality decline? Yes it does. Does it just work like ever before? Yes but I’m not sure I’ll answer it wholeheartedly. </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Goddamn Truth]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-05T22:12:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/that-goddamn-truth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/marcoarment">Marco Arment</a>:
<blockquote><p>I suspect the rapid decline of Apple’s software is a sign that marketing is too high a priority at Apple today: having major new releases every year is clearly impossible for the engineering teams to keep up with while maintaining quality. Maybe it’s an engineering problem, but I suspect not — I doubt that any cohesive engineering team could keep up with these demands and maintain significantly higher quality.</p></p><p><p>The problem seems to be quite simple: they’re doing too much, with unrealistic deadlines.</p></p><p><p>We don’t need major OS releases every year. We don’t need each OS release to have a huge list of new features. We need our computers, phones, and tablets to work well first so we can enjoy new features released at a healthy, gradual, sustainable pace.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>That goddamn truth! I don’t deny that iOS and OS X are rapidly growing over these 2 years. Many features and improvements they put at their software but it also increase the bugs, crashes and inconsistency. So many things are broken and need to be fixed. At least they need to slow down the software upgrade cycle and start to fix everything they broke.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Drafts for? - All This]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/whats-drafts-for/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-18T22:59:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/whats-drafts-for</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/drdrang">Dr. Drang</a> memberikan dua alasan mengapa <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/id/app/drafts-4-quickly-capture-notes/id905337691?mt=8&amp;uo=4">Drafts 4</a> layak berada di homescreen para pengguna perangkat iOS.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple vs Jailbreak]]></title>
    <link href="http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-01T23:03:00+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sweetdistraction.github.io/apple-vs-jailbreak</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.apple.com/legal/sales-support/sales-policies/retail_us.html">Apple</a>:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>Making unauthorized modifications to the software on an iPhone violates the iPhone software license agreement. The common term for modifying an iPhone is jail-breaking, with a particular emphasis on the second part of that term. That’s why we strongly, almost emphatically, recommend that you do not do so. Really. Should you be unable to use your iPhone due to an unauthorized software modification, its repair will not be covered under the warranty.</p></blockquote></p>

<p>Apple memang sudah lama menentang ataupun tak mengijinkan penggunanya untuk melakukan jailbreak. Pada halaman <em>sales policy</em> di atas bahkan Apple tak bertanggung jawab atas kerusakan yang terjadi akibat modifikasi dari sistem operasi iOS dalam hal ini berarti hangusnya garansi perangkat.</p>

<!--more-->

<p>Keputusan untuk melakukan jailbreak memang sepenuhnya ada di tangan pengguna dan tak selamanya jailbreak berdampak buruk. Bagi seorang pengembang ataupun seseorang yang ingin mempelajari tentang sistem operasi terutama iOS, jailbreak bisa saja merupakan sebuah langkah untuk mendukung kegiatannya. Tak hanya itu, jailbreak yang membuka akses <em>root</em> perangkat juga memungkinkan pengguna untuk mengkustomisasi perangkat yang dimiliki mulai dari menginstall tema, mengubah ikon batere atau sinyal, menghilangkan UI yang dianggap mengganggu dan masih banyak lagi. Namun juga tak jarang beberapa orang melakukan jailbreak untuk mengunduh dan menginstall aplikasi bajakan yang tentu saja merugikan bagi pengembang aplikasi padahal banyak cara untuk mendapatkan sebuah aplikasi secara legal, memakai iTunes gift card misalnya.</p>

<p>Memang secara teori, jailbreak bisa dihilangkan cukup dengan melakukan restore perangkat menggunakan iTunes apabila ingin melakukan klaim garansi, namun jika terjadi hal yang tak diinginkan semisal <em>brick</em> pada perangkat karena tak sengaja melakukan <em>Reset All Settings</em> maka siapa yang akan bertanggung jawab? Oleh sebab itu mengapa jailbreak selalu disertai dengan <em>disclaimer</em>: DWYOR (Do With Your Own Risk)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
